most O
frequently O
found O
associated O
with O
banana B-DISEASE
crown I-DISEASE
and O
fruit B-DISEASE
rot I-DISEASE
are O
Fusarium B-PATHOGEN
verticillioides I-PATHOGEN
and O
Fusarium B-PATHOGEN
musae I-PATHOGEN

By O
January B-DATE
2014 I-DATE
, O
approximately O
121 O
ha O
were O
affected O
. O

al O
. O
, O
2012 B-DATE
) O
. O

Tubers B-PLANT_PART
are O
either O
processed O
or O
fresh O
packed O
immediately O
following O
harvest O
or O
sent O
to O
storage O
. O

To O
confirm O
BBTV B-PATHOGEN
identification O
, O
polymerase O
chain O
reaction O
( O
PCR O
) O
was O
carried O
out O
using O
samples O
that O
previously O
tested O
positive O
by O
ELISA O
. O

J. O
Virol O
. O

F. B-PATHOGEN
kalimantanense I-PATHOGEN
was O
first O
reported O
associated O
with O
the O
pseudostems B-PLANT_PART
of O
Musa B-CROP
acuminata I-CROP
var O
. O

The O
relationship O
between O
DW O
and O
AIS O
was O
similar O
( O
AIS O
= O
0.00089 O
× O
DW O
) O
, O
and O
DW O
and O
AIS O
increased O
with O
time O
for O
most O
cultivars O
. O

Two O
symptomless O
plants O
tested O
negative O
. O

All O
three O
samples O
tested O
by O
ELISA O
were O
positive O
for O
BSV B-PATHOGEN
. O

The O
separation O
was O
achieved O
with O
a O
reverse O
phase O
C18 O
GraceSmart O
column O
( O
150 O
mm O
· O
4.6 O
mm O
, O
3 O
- O
mm O
particle O
size O
) O
from O
Grace B-ORG
Davison I-ORG
Discovery I-ORG
Sciences I-ORG
Corp I-ORG
( O
Deerfield B-GPE
, O
IL B-GPE
) O
. O

The O
sequence O
was O
similar O
( O
99.87 O
% O
) O
to O
that O
of O
B. B-PATHOGEN
cepacia I-PATHOGEN
genomovar O
III O
LMG O
12614 O
( O
GenBank B-ORG
Accession O
No O
. O
AF097532 O
) O
. O

Notably O
, O
we O
showed O
the O
first O
internal O
colonization O
of O
host O
plants O
with O
Rhodococcus O
sp O
. O
KB6 O
and O
discuss O
its O
potential O
as O
a O
biocontrol O
agent O
for O
sustainable O
agriculture O
. O

No O
significant O
change O
was O
observed O
in O
the O
composition O
of O
starch O
. O

Among O
foliar O
tissues O
of O
‘ O
Beauregard O
’ O
sweetpotatoes B-CROP
, O
the O
AA O
content O
was O
highest O
in O
young O
leaves B-PLANT_PART
( O
108 O
to O
139 O
mg/100 O
g O
fresh O
weight O
) O
and O
lowest O
in O
mature O
petioles B-PLANT_PART
( O
7.2 O
to O
13.9 O
mg O
) O
. O

Out O
of O
these O
five O
Homalotylus O
species O
, O
H. O
africanus O
is O
not O
reported O
from O
India B-GPE
( O
Noyes O
, O
2020 B-DATE
) O
. O

In O
2010 B-DATE
, O
US-23 O
again O
appeared O
but O
on O
tomato B-CROP
in O
two O
southeastern B-LOC
Wisconsin I-LOC
counties O
, O
Waukesha B-GPE
and O
Ozaukee B-GPE
, O
again O
in O
low O
incidence O
and O
severity O
. O

Recently O
, O
it O
has O
been O
demonstrated O
that O
acetone O
cyanohydrin O
is O
present O
in O
poorly O
processed O
cassava B-CROP
root B-PLANT_PART
food O
products O
. O

The O
disease O
resulted O
in O
a O
significant O
yield O
loss O
due O
to O
reduced O
fruit B-PLANT_PART
size O
. O

PVA B-PATHOGEN
and O
PVY B-PATHOGEN
were O
only O
detected O
in O
two O
localities O
. O

J. O
Virol O
. O

Pathogenicity O
of O
isolate O
GZF2 O
- O
2 O
was O
investigated O
to O
demonstrate O
Koch O
's O
postulate O
. O

Durability O
is O
the O
measure O
of O
the O
robustness O
of O
constructed O
facilities O
against O
deterioration O
tendencies O
. O

From O
June B-DATE
1992 I-DATE
to I-DATE
August I-DATE
1992 I-DATE
, O
70 O
patients O
presented O
to O
the O
provincial O
hospital O
in O
Chimoio B-GPE
, O
Manica B-GPE
Province I-GPE
, O
with O
a O
complaint O
of O
poisoning O
after O
eating O
bitter O
cassava B-CROP
. O

Banana B-CROP
( O
Musa B-CROP
spp I-CROP
. O
) O
is O
a O
popular O
fruit B-PLANT_PART
all O
over O
the O
world O
, O
and O
it O
's O
also O
an O
important O
cash O
crop O
with O
a O
planting O
area O
of O
358,924 O
ha O
in O
southern B-LOC
China I-LOC
. O

The O
study O
highlights O
the O
need O
for O
continuous O
monitoring O
of O
invasive O
whitefly O
species O
population O
on O
cassava B-CROP
for O
timely O
application O
of O
management O
practices O
to O
reduce O
the O
impact O
of O
cassava B-CROP
viral O
diseases O
and O
prevent O
potential O
yield O
losses O
. O

( O
2 O
) O
T. O
C. O
Vrain O
et O

Although O
all O
of O
the O
isolates O
tested O
were O
sensitive O
to O
fluopyram O
, O
the O
discovery O
of O
isolates O
resistant O
to O
boscalid O
and O
penthiopyrad O
suggests O
that O
all O
SDHI O
fungicides O
should O
be O
considered O
at O
high O
risk O
of O
resistance O
development O
in O
Michigan B-GPE
. O

The O
survival O
rate O
of O
the O
earthworms O
both O
> O
95 O
% O
, O
the O
highest O
number O
of O
cocoons O
( O
640.33 O
) O
and O
hatchlings O
( O
4694.33 O
) O
both O
in O
EW+EM O
( O
Earthworms O
added O
and O
EM O
inoculated O
) O
treatment O
. O

The O
higher O
fertilizer O
doses O
generated O
a O
major O
response O
in O
terms O
of O
micronutrient O
extraction O
by O
the O
banana B-CROP
plants O
. O

al O
. O

( O
3 O
) O
J. O
R. O
Xu O
et O

KF019184 O
and O
KF019185 O
) O
. O

In O
this O
article O
, O
we O
provide O
the O
status O
of O
recent O
research O
findings O
with O
regard O
to O
the O
CMD B-DISEASE
complex O
, O
present O
the O
molecular O
biology O
knowledge O
of O
CMGs B-PATHOGEN
with O
reference O
to O
other O
geminiviruses O
, O
and O
highlight O
the O
mechanisms O
by O
which O
CMGs B-PATHOGEN
have O
exploited O
nature O
to O
their O
advantage O
. O

( O
2 O
) O
T. O
Y. O
Zhang O
. O

Au O
cours O
d’un O
atelier O
d’une O
journée O
, O
un O
petit O
manuel O
d’instruction O
contenant O
un O
jeu O
de O
diapositives O
avec O
un O
texte O
, O
des O
cartes O
en O
couleur O
, O
des O
photos O
, O
des O
étapes O
du O
CPD O
concernant O
l’enfoncement O
du O
plastique O
, O
une O
note O
sur O
les O
insectes O
ainsi O
que O
des O
informations O
recommendées O
à O
la O
publication O
. O

No O
. O
66 O
. O

Prolonged O
and O
intensive O
exercise O
evoked O
a O
transient O
but O
robust O
increase O
in O
plasma O
levels O
of O
oxylipins O
, O
with O
a O
strong O
attenuation O
effect O
of O
ARA O
- O
CYP O
oxylipins O
linked O
to O
acute O
carbohydrate O
intake O
from O
bananas B-CROP
and O
2 B-DATE
- I-DATE
weeks I-DATE
ingestion O
of O
blueberries O
. O

With O
nitrate O
- O
nonutilizing O
( O
nit O
) O
mutants O
and O
testers O
for O
different O
vegetative O
compatibility O
groups O
( O
VCGs O
) O
, O
each O
of O
seven O
examined O
monospore O
isolates O
were O
placed O
in O
VCG O
01213 O
, O
which O
contains O
only O
strains O
of O
TR4 B-PATHOGEN
( O
3 O
) O
. O

This O
study O
provides O
important O
information O
on O
the O
genetic O
diversity O
of O
B. O
tabaci O
and O
B. O
afer O
in O
eastern B-LOC
DRC I-LOC
. O

Corky B-DISEASE
ringspot I-DISEASE
can O
result O
in O
substantial O
losses O
, O
with O
entire O
potato B-CROP
fields O
being O
rejected O
because O
of O
internal O
tuber B-PLANT_PART
damage O
. O

Spores O
at O
a O
concentration O
of O
106 O
spores O
per O
ml O
were O
suspended O
in O
an O
oil O
/ O
surfactant O
mixture O
and O
sprayed O
onto O
leaves B-PLANT_PART
until O
runoff O
. O

Therefore O
, O
sweetpotato B-CROP
breeding O
should O
involve O
the O
needs O
of O
stakeholders O
in O
the O
developing O
of O
new O
cultivars O
and O
new O
agricultural O
technologies O
to O
meet O
their O
diverse O
requirements O
( O
Atlin O
et O
al O
. O
, O
2001 B-DATE
; O
Rees O
et O
al O
. O
, O
2003 B-DATE
) O
. O

References O
: O
( O
1 O
) O
G. O
Loebenstein O
et O
al O
. O
, O
eds O
. O

The O
ZC B-DISEASE
CL514F O
/ O
R O
sequence O
( O
GenBank B-ORG
Accession O
No O
. O
FJ498807 O
) O
was O
98 O
% O
identical O
to O
analogous O
rplJ O
and O
rplL O
liberibacter O
ribosomal O
protein O
gene O
sequences O
amplified O
from O
several O
solanaceous B-CROP
plants I-CROP
in O
New B-GPE
Zealand I-GPE
( O
GenBank B-ORG
Accession O
Nos O
. O
EU834131 O
and O
EU935005 O
) O
. O

Conversely O
, O
water O
activity O
and O
° O
Brix O
were O
only O
affected O
by O
the O
amount O
of O
sugar O
. O

The O
first O
step O
to O
control O
fruit B-DISEASE
rots I-DISEASE
involves O
use O
of O
chemical O
fungicide O
in O
field O
and O
storage O
however O
, O
indiscriminate O
use O
of O
synthetic O
fungicides O
has O
been O
a O
major O
cause O
for O
development O
of O
resistant O
fungal O
strains O
, O
increased O
amounts O
of O
toxic O
residues O
in O
food O
products O
. O

The O
epidemic O
initiated O
on O
tomato B-CROP
in O
southern B-LOC
WI I-LOC
in O
early B-DATE
August I-DATE
and O
progressed O
northward O
in O
the O
state O
with O
additional O
reports O
on O
tomato B-CROP
primarily O
from O
home O
gardens O
and O
small O
farms O
. O

An O
experiment O
was O
established O
to O
study O
the O
rates O
of O
degeneration O
in O
selected O
cassava B-CROP
varieties O
Chereko O
, O
KBH2002_135 O
, O
Kipusa O
, O
Kizimbani O
, O
and O
Mkuranga1 O
and O
cultivars O
Kiroba O
and O
Kikombe O
under O
high O
- O
CBSD B-DISEASE
inoculum O
conditions O
in O
Bagamoyo B-GPE
, O
Tanzania B-GPE
from B-DATE
2013 I-DATE
to I-DATE
2017 I-DATE
. O

For O
sweetpotato B-CROP
skins O
, O
1 O
g O
of O
tissue O
was O
placed O
in O
a O
25 O
- O
mL O
erlenmeyer O
flask O
and O
10 O
mL O
of O
0.1 O
M O
HCl O
was O
added O
. O

Symptoms O
were O
not O
severe O
and O
were O
distributed O
sporadically O
in O
both O
locations O
. O

( O
4 O
) O
C. O
D. O
Smart O
et O

The O
infected O
root B-PLANT_PART
tubers B-PLANT_PART
are O
unfit O
for O
human O
consumption O
. O

The O
disease O
is O
caused O
by O
a O
soilborne O
fungus O
, O
Fusarium O
oxysporumSchlechtend O
. O
: O

Cienc O
. O

Int O
. O

( O
4 O
) O
R. B-CROP
C. I-CROP
Ploetz O
et O
al O
. O
, O
eds O
. O

( O
3 O
) O
R. O
D. O
Peters O
et O

al O
. O

The O
citrus O
mealybug O
( O
Planococus O
citri O
) O
has O
been O
shown O
to O
transmit O
banana B-PATHOGEN
streak I-PATHOGEN
virus I-PATHOGEN
( O
BSV B-PATHOGEN
) O
but O
not O
banana B-PATHOGEN
bunchy I-PATHOGEN
top I-PATHOGEN
virus I-PATHOGEN
or O
cucumber B-PATHOGEN
mosaic I-PATHOGEN
virus I-PATHOGEN
( O
CMV B-PATHOGEN
) O
( O
2 O
) O
. O

The O
membranes O
demonstrated O
their O
capacity O
for O
gaseous O
exchange O
and O
exhibited O
water O
- O
vapor O
permeability O
( O
WVP O
) O
rates O
comparable O
to O
injured O
skin O
one O
. O

Once O
found O
, O
fields O
must O
be O
considered O
permanently O
at O
risk O
to O
this O
disease O
due O
to O
the O
large O
host O
range O
of O
both O
the O
virus O
and O
the O
nematode O
vector O
. O

We O
report O
here O
data O
on O
a O
trio O
of O
tropical O
fruits B-PLANT_PART
, O
namely O
, O
banana B-CROP
, O
avocado B-CROP
, O
and O
mango B-CROP
. O

Inoculated O
plants O
were O
then O
placed O
in O
sand O
in O
3 O
- O
liter O
pots O
under O
28 O
° O
C O
, O
70 O
% O
relative O
humidity O
, O
and O
a B-DATE
16/8 I-DATE
- I-DATE
h I-DATE
light O
/ O
darkness O
photoperiod O
. O

All O
AG-3 O
, O
AG-4 O
and O
AG-5 O
isolates O
tested O
caused O
rhizoctonia B-DISEASE
disease I-DISEASE
symptoms O
on O
the O
potato B-CROP
cultivar O
Coliban O
in O
pathogenicity O
trials O
conducted O
under O
glasshotise O
conditions O
. O

Considered O
overall O
, O
these O
results O
confirm O
the O
increasing O
threat O
that O
CBSD B-DISEASE
poses O
to O
cassava B-CROP
production O
in O
DRC B-GPE
and O
describe O
an O
important O
expansion O
in O
the O
African B-LOC
pandemic O
of O
CBSD B-DISEASE
. O

J. O
Virol O
. O

All O
the O
genes O
were O
induced O
expression O
in O
tuber B-PLANT_PART
skins O
by O
white O
light O
, O
and O
followed O
by O
anthocyanin O
accumulation O
. O

The O
isolate O
, O
designated O
INSV O
pot O
1 O
, O
was O
mechanically O
inoculated O
to O
one O
plant O
of O
potato B-CROP
cv O
. O

al O
. O

no O
. O

The O
presence O
of O
the O
virus O
poses O
a O
challenge O
to O
the O
dissemination O
of O
planting O
materials O
in O
the O
region O
because O
begomovirus O
- O
infected O
plants O
often O
do O
not O
show O
symptoms O
. O

Cavendish B-CROP
banana I-CROP
is O
the O
second O
most O
cultivated O
species O
in O
Malaysia B-GPE
due O
to O
its O
high O
potassium O
and O
vitamin O
B6 O
content O
. O

The O
feasibility O
of O
using O
banana B-CROP
peel O
for O
the O
production O
of O
cellulase O
by O
Trichoderma O
viride O
GIM O
3.0010 O
in O
solid O
- O
state O
fermentation O
was O
evaluated O
in O
this O
study O
. O

However O
, O
they O
indicate O
an O
ongoing O
adaptation O
process O
of O
BtMEAM1 O
to O
cassava B-CROP
, O
increasing O
the O
likelihood O
of O
begomovirus O
emergence O
in O
this O
crop O
in O
the O
near O
future O
. O

The O
same O
symptom O
was O
observed O
after O
14 B-DATE
days I-DATE
on O
all O
roots B-PLANT_PART
( O
n O
= O
20 O
) O
inoculated O
with O
the O
pathogen O
. O

( O
Watanabe O
et O
al O
. O
2013 B-DATE
) O
. O

All O
isolates O
caused O
mortality O
of O
the O
larval O
stages O
, O
whereas O
the O
adults O
appeared O
resistant O
to O
nematode O
infection O
. O

CABI B-ORG
Publishing I-ORG
. O

in O
non O
- O
host O
plants O
and O
their O
potential O
role O
in O
the O
Fusarium B-DISEASE
wilt I-DISEASE
disease I-DISEASE
of O
banana B-CROP
. O

In O
Colombia B-GPE
, O
although O
different O
varieties O
exist O
in O
the O
market O
, O
the O
Dominico B-CROP
Hartón I-CROP
plantain I-CROP
has O
the O
highest O
volume O
of O
commercialization O
. O

( O
2 O
) O
Q. O
J. O
Liu O
et O

Recently O
, O
leaf B-PLANT_PART
symptoms O
characteristic O
of O
banana B-DISEASE
streak I-DISEASE
disease I-DISEASE
( O
1 O
) O
were O
found O
on O
banana B-CROP
cv O
. O

The O
chimeric O
gene O
was O
placed O
under O
the O
control O
of O
the O
granule O
- O
bound O
- O
starch O
synthase O
promoter O
. O

Entomol O
. O

The O
pathogen O
was O
confirmed O
as O
P. B-PATHOGEN
infestans I-PATHOGEN
on O
the O
basis O
of O
morphological O
characters O
( O
1 O
) O
. O

Leaves B-PLANT_PART
from O
10 O
symptomatic O
and O
three O
symptomless O
plants O
were O
sampled O
from O
each O
field O
and O
tested O
by O
double O
antibody O
sandwich O
( O
DAS)-ELISA O
( O
1 O
) O
at O
ARI O
- O
Uyole O
. O

al O
. O

J. O
Plant O
Pathol O
. O

Control O
pots O
were O
not O
inoculated O
. O

Data O
collected O
in O
Munyika B-GPE
show O
that O
when O
appropriate O
cultural O
practices O
are O
applied O
and O
adhered O
to O
, O
within O
a B-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
BBTD B-DISEASE
incidence O
can O
be O
reduced O
to O
economically O
acceptable O
levels O
in O
an O
existing O
plantation O
( O
26.2 O
% O
to O
8.2 O
% O
) O
and O
in O
new O
plantations O
( O
2 O
% O
, O
FHIA O
trial O
) O
. O

In O
early B-DATE
months I-DATE
of I-DATE
2020 I-DATE
, O
the O
cassava O
mealybug O
( O
CMB O
) O
Phenacoccus O
manihoti O
Matile O
- O
Ferrero O
( O
Hemiptera O
: O
Pseudococcidae O
) O
, O
known O
as O
the O
most O
destructive O
pests O
of O
cassava B-CROP
in O
the O
world O
, O
was O
reported O
from O
Thrissur B-GPE
, O
Kerala B-GPE
( O
Joshi O
et O
al O
. O
2020 B-DATE
) O
. O

( O
2 O
) O
S. O
B. O
Goodwin O
et O

The O
pathogen O
was O
cultured O
on O
carnation O
leaf O
agar O
( O
CLA O
) O
for O
10 B-DATE
days I-DATE
at O
25 O
° O
C O
with O
a O
12 B-DATE
- I-DATE
h I-DATE
photoperiod O
. O

References O
: O
( O
1 O
) O
A.M. O
Golden O
and O
W. O
Birchfield O
. O

TR4 B-PATHOGEN
was O
not O
isolated O
from O
asymptomatic O
control O
plants O
. O

Methods O
We O
performed O
a O
country O
- O
wide O
whitefly O
diversity O
study O
in O
cassava B-CROP
in O
Brazil B-GPE
. O

The O
main O
species O
known O
to O
affect O
cassava B-CROP
are O
M. O
incognita O
and O
M. O
javanica O
( O
Coyne O
and O
Affokpon O
, O
2018 B-DATE
) O
. O

One O
was O
targeting O
the O
aspartic O
protease O
( O
AP O
) O
and O
reverse O
transcription O
( O
RT O
) O
regions O
of O
ORF3 O
using O
primer O
pair O
BSV O
4673 O
( O
5′-GGAATGAAAGAGCAGGCC-3′ O
) O
and O
BSV O
5317 O
( O
5′-AGTCATTGGGTYCAACCTCTGTCCC-3′ O
) O
with O
an O
amplicon O
size O
of O
644 O
bp O
( O
Manoranjitham O
et O
al O
. O
2012 B-DATE
) O
. O

A O
qPCR O
study O
indicated O
that O
both O
SPITI O
genes O
were O
expressed O
in O
all O
the O
sample O
tissues O
, O
though O
relative O
expression O
values O
differed O
across O
tissues O
at O
different O
developmental O
stages O
. O

The O
disease O
was O
also O
observed O
in O
neighboring O
greenhouses O
by O
the B-DATE
spring I-DATE
of I-DATE
2010 I-DATE
. O

Plants O
were O
covered O
by O
polyethylene O
bags O
for O
2 B-DATE
days I-DATE
to O
achieve O
high O
humidity O
levels O
and O
maintained O
in O
a O
greenhouse O
at O
25 O
± O
2 O
° O
C O
. O

Nutrient O
extraction O
curves O
in O
plants O
are O
useful O
for O
defining O
optimal O
doses O
of O
macroand O
micronutrients O
( O
Medina O
, O
2010 B-DATE
; O
Jeyabaskaran O
et O
al O
. O
, O
2018 B-DATE
) O
. O

Hortic O
. O

This O
virus O
is O
a O
member O
of O
the O
genus O
Tobravirus O
and O
is O
transmitted O
by O
a O
number O
of O
species O
of O
stubby O
- O
root O
nematodes O
( O
Paratrichodorus O
or O
Trichodorus O
spp O
. O
) O
. O

However O
, O
a O
number O
of O
constraints O
including O
pests O
and O
diseases O
were O
reported O
to O
be O
affecting O
cassava B-CROP
growing O
. O

Williams O
durante O
dos O
ciclos O
productivos O
en O
el O
Urabá B-GPE
, I-GPE
Colombia B-GPE
. O

To O
confirm O
the O
positive O
PCR O
result O
, O
the O
genome O
of O
the O
virus O
was O
enriched O
by O
rolling O
- O
circle O
amplification O
( O
RCA O
) O
using O
a O
TempliPhi O
100 O
RCA O
Kit O
( O
GE B-ORG
Healthcare I-ORG
, O
U.S.A. B-GPE
) O
. O

Cassava B-DISEASE
brown I-DISEASE
streak I-DISEASE
disease I-DISEASE
( O
CBSD B-DISEASE
) O
of O
cassava B-CROP
( O
Manihot B-CROP
esculenta I-CROP
) O
caused O
by O
cassava B-PATHOGEN
brown I-PATHOGEN
streak I-PATHOGEN
virus I-PATHOGEN
( O
CBSV B-PATHOGEN
) O
has O
been O
known O
in O
Tanzania B-GPE
since O
the B-DATE
1930s I-DATE
, O
but O
has O
not O
been O
recorded O
previously O
in O
Mozambique B-GPE
. O

The O
disease O
incidence O
was O
about O
0.5 O
% O
at O
the O
surveyed O
field O
. O

It O
was O
identified O
as O
a O
subgroup O
I O
CMV B-PATHOGEN
based O
on O
its O
reaction O
to O
CMV O
DTL- O
, O
but O
not O
CMV O
ToRS- O
monoclonal O
antibodies O
in O
double O
antibody O
sandwich O
( O
DAS)-enzyme O
- O
linked O
immunosorbent O
assay O
( O
ELISA O
) O
. O

St. B-GPE
Paul I-GPE
, O
MN B-GPE
, O
1996 B-DATE
. O

Yet O
, O
even O
under O
these O
adverse O
conditions O
we O
could O
report O
, O
in O
a O
single O
sweep O
, O
from O
1000 O
to O
3000 O
unique O
gene O
products O
. O

Mainland B-LOC
China I-LOC
is O
one O
of O
the O
leading O
producers O
of O
Cavendish B-CROP
bananas I-CROP
, O
and O
to O
satisfy O
local O
demand O
for O
the O
fruit B-PLANT_PART
, O
commercial O
production O
is O
expanding O
into O
neighbouring O
countries O
such O
as O
Laos B-GPE
, O
Myanmar B-GPE
and O
Vietnam B-GPE
. O

( O
3 O
) O
N. O
Rosenzweig O
et O
al O
. O

Supply O
of O
nitrogen O
increased O
the O
cyanogenic O
glucoside O
concentration O
in O
the O
shoot B-PLANT_PART
apex O
. O

Compared O
with O
the O
end O
of O
treatment O
, O
the O
above O
- O
mentioned O
indexes O
recurred O
insignificantly O
in O
the O
combination O
group O
and O
acupuncture O
group O
after O
64 B-DATE
weeks I-DATE
of O
follow O
- O
up O
( O
P>0.05 O
) O
, O
but O
all O
recurred O
significantly O
in O
the O
Plantain B-CROP
and O
Senna O
Granule O
group O
( O
P>0.05 O
) O
. O

Isolate O
Mp O
1 O
induced O
the O
longest O
lesion O
( O
7.2 O
cm O
) O
, O
followed O
by O
Mp O
4 O
( O
4.1 O
cm O
) O
, O
Mp O
3 O
and O
Mp O
5 O
( O
3.8 O
cm O
each O
) O
, O
and O
Mp O
2 O
( O
1.2 O
cm O
) O
. O

al O
. O

Further O
research O
is O
needed O
to O
determine O
if O
BBrMV B-PATHOGEN
infecting O
ginger B-CROP
poses O
a O
threat O
to O
banana B-CROP
, O
edible B-CROP
ginger I-CROP
, O
and O
other O
closely O
related O
ornamentals O
in O
Hawaii B-GPE
. O

al O
. O

A O
potato O
CMV B-PATHOGEN
isolate O
, O
PoCMV7 O
- O
5 O
, O
readily O
infected O
solanaceous O
plants O
in O
which O
it O
induced O
systemic O
infection O
, O
but O
was O
less O
infectious O
to O
other O
hosts O
including O
those O
of O
Leguminosae O
and O
Cucurbitaceae O
. O

Agriculturalists O
identified O
it O
as O
a O
strain O
high O
193 O

Roots B-PLANT_PART
were O
covered O
with O
5 O
cm O
of O
fumigated O
Tifton O
loamy O
sand O
( O
fine O
- O
loamy O
, O
siliceous O
, O
thermic O
Plinthic O
Kandiudults O
) O
. O

The O
amplicons O
of O
expected O
size O
were O
obtained O
from O
17 O
of O
90 O
samples O
analyzed O
( O
18.8 O
% O
) O
. O

In O
the O
ﬁeld O
studies O
, O
natural O
drought O
conditions O
and O
selective O
irrigation O
were O
used O
to O
impose O
water O
deprivation O
during O
the O
critical O
SR O
formation O
period O
. O

This O
is O
the O
first O
confirmed O
diagnosis O
of O
CMV B-PATHOGEN
on O
bananas B-CROP
in O
South B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
. O

Both O
Pectobacterium B-PATHOGEN
atrosepticum I-PATHOGEN
( O
Pba O
) O
and O
P. B-PATHOGEN
carotovorum I-PATHOGEN
subsp O
. O
… O

Cyanogenic O
glycosides O
, O
linamarin O
and O
lotaustralin O
, O
are O
presents O
in O
all O
tissues O
of O
Cassava B-PATHOGEN
( O
Manihot B-CROP
esculenta I-CROP
Crantz O
) O
except O
seeds B-PLANT_PART
and O
function O
as O
a O
deterrent O
for O
herbivores O
as O
well O
as O
the O
translocable O
form O
of O
reduced O
nitrogen O
. O

Cassava B-PATHOGEN
brown I-PATHOGEN
streak I-PATHOGEN
virus I-PATHOGEN
( O
CBSV B-PATHOGEN
) O
isolates O
were O
analysed O
from O
symptomatic O
cassava B-CROP
collected O
between O
1997 B-DATE
and I-DATE
2008 I-DATE
in O
the O
major O
cultivation O
regions O
of O
East B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
. O

After O
4 B-DATE
weeks I-DATE
, O
all O
plants O
inoculated O
with O
the O
isolates O
from O
Pakistan B-GPE
, O
Lebanon B-GPE
, O
and O
TR4 B-PATHOGEN
( O
II-5 O
) O
produced O
typical O
symptoms O
of O
Fusarium B-DISEASE
wilt I-DISEASE
. O

After O
4 B-DATE
weeks I-DATE
, O
TR4 B-PATHOGEN
- O
treated O
plants O
were O
dead O
, O
whereas O
controls O
remained O
healthy O
. O

Four B-DATE
days I-DATE
later I-DATE
, O
five O
stem B-PLANT_PART
tops O
of O
sweetpotato B-CROP
were O
injected O
with O
a O
bacteria O
suspension O
( O
108 O
CFU O
/ O
ml O
) O
of O
approximately O
100 O
μl O
to O
fulfill O
Koch O
's O
postulates O
. O

Microbiol O
. O

However O
, O
farmer O
access O
to O
brewers O
’ O
grains O
is O
limited O
to O
the O
immediate O
area O
in O
which O
beer O
factories O
are O
found O
. O

B. B-PATHOGEN
setariae I-PATHOGEN
is O
one O
of O
the O
most O
important O
pathogens O
of O
lawn B-CROP
grass I-CROP
, O
gramineous B-CROP
crops I-CROP
, O
and O
other O
plants O
( O
1,3 O
) O
. O

Streptomyces B-PATHOGEN
europaeiscabiei I-PATHOGEN
was O
the O
predominant O
species O
found O
. O

( O
Weir O
et O
al O
. O
2012 B-DATE
) O
. O

Taken O
together O
, O
our O
results O
confirm O
the O
presence O
of O
TR4 B-PATHOGEN
in O
Colombia B-GPE
. O

References O
: O
( O
1 O
) O
M. O
A. O
Dita O
et O
al O
. O

Received O
: O
28 O
- O
09 O
- O
2020 O
Accepted O
: O
02 O
- O
12 O
- O
2020 O
Published O
: O
21 O
- O
01 O
- O
202 O

J. O
Virol O
. O

Previously O
published O
ITS O
sequences O
from O
R. B-PATHOGEN
oryzae I-PATHOGEN
strains O
were O
included O
for O
reference O
, O
and O
Mucor O
miehei O
( O
Accession O
No O
. O
AF198253 O
) O
was O
used O
as O
an O
out O
- O
group O
( O
Abe O
et O
al O
. O
, O
2006 B-DATE
) O
. O

The O
crop O
is O
very O
suitable O
for O
these O
conditions O
because O
of O
its O
exceptional O
tolerance O
to O
drought O
and O
to O
acid O
, O
infertile O
soils O
. O

Subsequently O
, O
fine O
chlorotic O
streaks O
were O
observed O
in O
leaves B-PLANT_PART
of O
Cavendish B-CROP
banana I-CROP
in O
several O
fields O
in O
southern B-LOC
Taiwan I-LOC
. O

Of O
the O
samples O
tested O
, O
27 O
were O
positive O
for O
BBTV B-PATHOGEN
using O
DAS O
- O
ELISA O
. O

A O
large O
experiment O
was O
conducted O
to O
quantify O
ID O
in O
cassava B-CROP
. O

Abstract O
The O
present O
study O
characterizes O
Bemisia O
tabaci O
and O
Bemisia O
afer O
from O
cassava B-CROP
in O
eastern B-LOC
Democratic I-LOC
Republic I-LOC
of I-LOC
Congo I-LOC
( O
DRC B-GPE
) O
. O

Plant O
Dis O
. O

Although O
EMDV B-PATHOGEN
is O
widespread O
in O
the O
Mediterranean B-LOC
region I-LOC
and O
the O
Middle B-LOC
East I-LOC
( O
Brunt O
et O
al O
. O
, O
1996 B-DATE
) O
, O
and O
has O
recently O
been O
reported O
in O
mainland B-LOC
Spain I-LOC
( O
Aramburu O
et O
al O
. O
, O
2006 B-DATE
) O
, O
this O
is O
the O
first O
report O
of O
EMDV B-PATHOGEN
in O
Slovenia B-GPE
. O

For O
all O
five O
cultivars O
, O
N. B-PATHOGEN
mangiferae I-PATHOGEN
significantly O
( O
P O
< O
0.05 O
) O
reduced O
plant O
height O
and O
number O
of O
shoots B-PLANT_PART
and O
roots B-PLANT_PART
, O
compared O
with O
control O
plants O
. O

Flowers B-PLANT_PART
showed O
significant O
cupping O
and O
browning O
and O
growers O
report O
a O
reduction O
in O
size O
and O
shelf O
life O
. O

Studying O
the O
effect O
of O
pH O
on O
the O
growth O
of O
several O
crops O
grown O
in O
flowing O
nutrient O
solution O
, O

Plant O
Pathol O
. O

Sequence O
analyses O
of O
partial O
16S O
rDNA O
fragments O
showed O
that O
Vietnamese B-GPE
CWB B-PATHOGEN
phytoplasmas I-PATHOGEN
have O
99 O
% O
similarity O
with O
‘ O
Candidatus B-PATHOGEN
Phytoplasma I-PATHOGEN
asteris I-PATHOGEN
’ O
. O

In O
Brazil B-GPE
, O
anthracnose B-DISEASE
by O
C. B-PATHOGEN
chrysophillum I-PATHOGEN
was O
reported O
in O
cashew B-CROP
( O
Veloso O
et O
al O
. O
, O
2018 B-DATE
) O
and O
banana B-CROP
trees O
( O
Vieira O
et O
al O
. O
, O
2017 B-DATE
) O
. O

Phytopathology O
85:436 O
, O
1995 B-DATE
. O

A O
total O
of O
164 O
banana B-CROP
plant O
samples O
with O
bunchy O
top O
, O
stunting O
and O
leaf B-PLANT_PART
samples O
with O
green O
streak O
symptoms O
were O
collected O
. O

TR4 B-PATHOGEN
was O
also O
confirmed O
in O
symptomatic O
tissues O
by O
specific O
PCR O
analysis O
( O
Dita O
et O
al O
. O
2010 B-DATE
) O
and O
sequencing O
of O
the O
amplified O
band O
. O

The O
incidence O
of O
the O
disease O
was O
up O
to O
50 O
% O
and O
found O
to O
occur O
at O
an O
altitude O
up O
to O
3000 O
m O
asl O
. O

To O
our O
knowledge O
, O
this O
is O
the O
first O
report O
of O
the O
occurrence O
of O
homothallic O
P. B-PATHOGEN
infestans I-PATHOGEN
isolates O
in O
commercial O
potato B-CROP
crops O
( O
S. B-CROP
tuberosum I-CROP
) O
in O
the O
Toluca B-GPE
Valley I-GPE
, O
Mexico B-GPE
. O

al O
. O
Virol O
. O

In O
the O
new O
spread O
zone O
of O
Haut B-GPE
- I-GPE
Katanga I-GPE
, O
incidence O
increased O
from O
1.7 O
% O
to O
15.9 O
% O
. O

in O
West B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
. O

Pasture B-CROP
herbs I-CROP
can O
increase O
pasture O
production O
and O
feed O
quality O
over O
summer O
when O
ryegrass B-CROP
based O
pasture O
often O
constrains O
livestock O
production O
. O

( O
2 O
) O
D. O
Geiser O
et O

( O
3 O
) O
K. O
L. O
Perry O
et O
al O
. O

Phytopathology O
101 O
: O
S162 O
, O
2011 B-DATE
. O

These O
data O
represent O
one O
of O
the O
first O
uses O
of O
a O
single O
- O
copy O
nuclear O
gene O
in O
a O
plant O
phylogeographic O
study O
and O
yield O
several O
important O
insights O
into O
cassava B-CROP
's O
evolutionary O
origin O
: O
( O
i O
) O
cassava B-CROP
was O
likely O
domesticated O
from O
wild B-CROP
M. I-CROP
esculenta I-CROP
populations O
along O
the O
southern B-LOC
border I-LOC
of I-LOC
the I-LOC
Amazon I-LOC
basin I-LOC
; O
( O
ii O
) O
the O
crop O
does O
not O
seem O
to O
be O
derived O
from O
several O
progenitor O
species O
, O
as O
previously O
proposed O
; O
and O
( O
iii O
) O
cassava B-CROP
does O
not O
share O
haplotypes O
with O
Manihot B-CROP
pruinosa I-CROP
, O
a O
closely O
related O
, O
potentially O
hybridizing O
species O
. O

Phytophthora B-PATHOGEN
infestans I-PATHOGEN
causes O
severe O
symptoms O
of O
wilt B-DISEASE
disease I-DISEASE
on O
potato B-CROP
crops O
( O
Solanum B-CROP
tuberosum I-CROP
) O
in O
the O
Toluca B-GPE
Valley I-GPE
( O
Mexico B-GPE
) O
despite O
the O
use O
of O
fungicides O
. O

A O
total O
of O
94 O
isolates O
of O
Colletotrichum B-PATHOGEN
sp I-PATHOGEN
. O
were O
obtained O
from O
cultivated O
cassava B-CROP
and O
15 O
from O
wild O
species O
. O

Eur O
. O

In O
early B-DATE
1999 I-DATE
, O
the O
first O
severe O
outbreak O
of O
BSV B-PATHOGEN
infection O
in O
commercial O
export O
bananas B-CROP
( O
Musa B-CROP
AAA O
cv O
. O

References O
: O
( O
1 O
) O
R. O
J. O
Bandoni O
. O

CsVX B-PATHOGEN
was O
not O
detected O
in O
any O
of O
the O
plants O
collected O
in O
the O
other O
surveyed O
areas O
. O

Additional O
keywords O
: O
crop O
management O
; O
yield O
; O
overturned O
; O
phytonematodes O
; O
bioregulators O
. O

Banana B-CROP
is O
the O
fourth O
ranked O
horticulture O
crop O
in O
the O
world O
and O
first O
among O
the O
fruits B-PLANT_PART
( O
Surya O
Prabha O
and O
Satheesh O
Kumar O
, O
2015 B-DATE
) O
. O

Disease O
symptoms O
associated O
with O
US-23 O
were O
observed O
exclusively O
on O
potato B-CROP
in O
2009 B-DATE
and O
on O
tomato B-CROP
in O
2010 B-DATE
in O
Wisconsin B-GPE
. O

Design O
/ O
methodology O
/ O
approach O
: O

The O
presence O
of O
the O
fungus O
in O
the O
samples O
was O
confirmed O
by O
PCR O
analysis O
of O
DNA O
extracted O
from O
symptomatic O
leaves B-PLANT_PART
with O
a O
M. B-PATHOGEN
fijiensis I-PATHOGEN
- O
specific O
ITS O
- O
based O
primer O
pair O
( O
2 O
) O
. O

The O
RT O
reactions O
were O
done O
using O
both O
random O
and O
oligo O
dT O
primers O
. O

Further O
investigations O
are O
required O
to O
determine O
the O
epidemiological O
significance O
of O
M. B-CROP
lutea I-CROP
in O
the O
CMB B-DISEASE
- O
cassava B-CROP
pathosystem O
. O

Pathogenicity O
assay O
was O
conducted O
using O
1 B-DATE
- I-DATE
month I-DATE
- I-DATE
old I-DATE
banana B-CROP
plants O
( O
cv O
. O

( O
2 O
) O
J. O
M. O
Crosslin O
and O
P. O
E. O
Thomas O
. O

References O
: O
( O
1 O
) O
D. O
C. O
Erwin O
and O
O. O
K. O
Ribeiro O
, O
Page O
346 O
in O
: O
Phytophthora O
Diseases O
Worldwide O
. O

J. O
Virol O
. O

A O
3 O
- O
year O
- O
old O
comatose O
child O
died O
soon O
after O
admission O
, O
probably O
from O
aspiration O
pneumonia O
after O
vomiting O
. O

Sensitive O
and O
resistant O
F. B-PATHOGEN
sambucinum I-PATHOGEN
and O
F. B-PATHOGEN
oxysporum I-PATHOGEN
isolates O
were O
reported O
. O

No.1 O
. O

al O
. O

This O
study O
reports O
the O
first O
comprehensive O
analysis O
on O
how O
evolution O
is O
shaping O
the O
populations O
of O
CBSV B-PATHOGEN
and O
UCBSV B-PATHOGEN
. O

Banana B-CROP
fritters O
were O
analysed O
for O
moisture O
and O
fat O
contents O
, O
moisture O
loss O
, O
colour O
, O
hardness O
and O
sensory O
characteristics O
. O

However O
, O
no O
primary O
parasitoid O
of O
the O
cassava O
mealybug O
was O
observed O
so O
far O
. O

Our O
objectives O
were O
to O
( O
1 O
) O
confirm O
and O
quantify O
the O
level O
of O
herbicide O
resistance O
in O
the O
buckhorn B-CROP
plantain I-CROP
population O
using O
dose O
- O
response O
experiments O
and O
( O
2 O
) O
find O
alternative O
herbicides O
that O
could O
be O
used O
to O
control O
this O
population O
. O

Single O
colonies O
were O
picked O
and O
re O
- O
streaked O
onto O
new O
LB O
medium O
. O

, O
, O
the O
latter O
in O
a O
proprietary O
material O
( O
Miller O
, O
1988 B-DATE
) O
. O

A O
non O
- O
infected O
banana B-CROP
plant O
was O
included O
in O
the O
test O
as O
a O
healthy O
control O
. O

Rep. O
52:423 O
, O
1968 B-DATE
. O

Theoretical O
implications O
: O
Using O
participation O
as O
a O
means O
to O
achieve O
predetermined O
strategies O
lead O
to O
failure O
and O
conflict O
in O
development O
programmes O
while O
as O
consulting O
with O
, O
and O
listening O
to O
farmers O
has O
potential O
to O
increase O
their O
cooperation O
in O
development O
programmes O
. O

To O
our O
knowledge O
, O
this O
is O
the O
first O
report O
of O
BBrMV B-PATHOGEN
in O
Ecuador B-GPE
and O
the O
first O
BBrMV B-PATHOGEN
partial O
nucleotide O
sequence O
reported O
from O
the O
Americas O
. O

In O
chapter O
1 O
, O
I O
describe O
the O
current O
state O
of O
art O
of O
banana B-CROP
research O
and O
the O
related O
Fusarium B-PATHOGEN
pathogens I-PATHOGEN
. O

Plant O
Dis O
. O
96:454 O
, O
2012 B-DATE
. O

These O
districts O
were O
selected O
because O
of O
the O
importance O
of O
sweetpotato B-CROP
production O
in O
their O
food O
production O
( O
Ndamage O
et O
al O
. O
, O
1992 B-DATE
) O
. O

This O
was O
characterized O
by O
localized O
white O
discoloured O
segmentation O
of O
the O
cervical O
groove O
, O
moreover O
, O
after O
cooking O
the O
prawns O
exploded O
, O
making O
them O
unfit O
for O
commercial O
sale O
. O

During O
2006 B-DATE
harvests O
an O
S1 O
plant O
produced O
roots B-PLANT_PART
that O
stained O
brownish O
- O
red O
when O
treated O
with O
an O
iodine O
solution O
, O
suggesting O
that O
it O
had O
lower O
- O
than O
- O
normal O
levels O
of O
amylose O
in O
its O
starch O
. O

Occurrence O
of O
the O
disease O
on O
some O
banana B-CROP
cultivars O
in O
Georgia O
provides O
useful O
information O
to O
potential O
producers O
, O
and O
the O
cultivars O
that O
were O
observed O
to O
be O
resistant O
to O
the O
disease O
may O
be O
more O
suitable O
for O
production O
. O

110:309 O
, O
2004 B-DATE
. O

In O
this O
paper O
, O
we O
examined O
the O
ability O
to O
induce O
RNA O
interference O
( O
RNAi O
) O
in O
the O
banana O
weevil O
via O
feeding O
. O

In O
this O
respect O
, O
sweetpotato B-CROP
will O
be O
a O
solution O
to O
solving O
problems O
such O
as O
food O
, O
energy O
, O
health O
, O
and O
environment O
facing O
the O
globe O
in O
the B-DATE
21st I-DATE
century I-DATE
. O

Another O
source O
of O
bypass O
protein O
is O
cassava B-CROP
foliage.3‒6 B-PLANT_PART

Crop O
Prot O
. O

Confocal O
microscopy O
confirmed O
expression O
in O
spermagonia O
in O
leaf B-PLANT_PART
substomatal O
cavities O
, O
consistent O
with O
a O
role O
in O
sexual O
reproduction O
. O

The O
objective O
of O
this O
study O
was O
to O
determine O
the O
ascorbic O
acid O
, O
thiamin O
, O
riboflavin O
, O
and O
vitamin O
B6 O
content O
in O
a O
wide O
range O
of O
edible O
tissues O
of O
‘ O
Beauregard O
’ O
and O
‘ O
LA O
07 O
- O
146 O
’ O
sweetpotatoes B-CROP
, O
two O
important O
commercial O
cultivars O
in O
Louisiana O
. O

Bananas B-CROP
( O
Musa B-CROP
spp I-CROP
. O
) O
are O
one O
of O
world O
's O
most O
popular O
fruits B-PLANT_PART
, O
and O
China B-GPE
is O
the O
third O
largest O
banana B-CROP
- O
producing O
country O
in O
the O
world O
. O

BLAST O
analysis O
showed O
100 O
% O
identity O
to O
' O
Ca O
. O

al O
. O

In O
Colombia B-GPE
, O
the O
income O
of O
about O
150 O
thousand O
families O
depends O
on O
the O
production O
of O
banana B-CROP
for O
export O
( O
Red O
Agricola O
, O
2020 B-DATE
) O
, O
and O
Uraba B-GPE
is O
the O
principal O
producing O
region O
of O
the O
country O
. O

In O
October B-DATE
1995 I-DATE
, O
storage O
roots B-PLANT_PART
of O
sweetpotato B-CROP
cv O
. O

Also O
, O
consistent O
with O
the O
theory O
of O
planned O
behavior O
( O
TPB O
) O
, O
all O
its O
dimensions O
( O
attitude O
, O
subjective O
norms O
and O
perceived O
behavioral O
control O
) O
affected O
the O
adoption O
of O
SAPs O
. O

To O
the O
best O
of O
our O
knowledge O
, O
Clostridium O
sensu O
stricto O
cluster O
1 O
and O
Lysinibacillus O
in O
fufu O
, O
and O
Brevundimonas O
, O
Cupriavidus O
, O
Sphingomonas O
and O
Strenotrophomomas O
in O
garri O
are O
reported O
for O
the O
first O
time O
. O

Plant O
Dis O
. O
78:101 O
. O
1994 B-DATE
. O

The O
incidence O
level O
was O
about O
22 O
% O
, O
mainly O
on O
the O
old O
leaves B-PLANT_PART
. O

74:5862 O
, O
2008 B-DATE
. O

Two O
pieces O
were O
used O
as O
rootstocks O
in O
graft O
- O
inoculation O
tests O
with O
Secundina O
scions B-PLANT_PART
for O
FSD B-DISEASE
detection O
, O
and O
two O
pieces O
were O
potted O
in O
sterilized O
soil O
to O
be O
used O
in O
other O
tests O
. O

Seventy O
percent O
of O
the O
cassava B-CROP
output O
is O
used O
for O
starch O
and O
ethanol O
production O
and O
it O
has O
become O
the O
base O
of O
food O
and O
bioenergy O
industries O
. O

1B O
- O
C O
) O
. O

A O
Grande O
Naine O
( O
Cavendish O
, O
AAA O
) O
plant O
with O
typical O
infectious B-DISEASE
chlorosis I-DISEASE
disease I-DISEASE
was O
obtained O
from O
Letsitele B-GPE
. O

Phytopathology O
96:838 O
, O
2006 B-DATE
. O

This O
is O
the O
first O
report O
of O
C. B-PATHOGEN
lunata I-PATHOGEN
pathogenic O
on O
cassava B-CROP
. O

The O
most O
important O
sweetpotato B-CROP
cultivar O
traits O
had O
high O
yield O
, O
early O
maturity O
, O
drought O
tolerance O
, O
disease O
and O
pest O
tolerance O
, O
and O
good O
culinary O
taste O
at O
22.5 O
% O
, O
18.5 O
% O
, O
15.4 O
% O
, O
12.7 O
% O
, O
and O
10.1 O
% O
, O
respectively O
. O

96:1323 O
, O
2012 B-DATE
. O

Potato B-CROP
production O
is O
concentrated O
in O
the O
southern B-LOC
highlands I-LOC
and O
mainly O
carried O
out O
by O
smallholder O
farmers O
. O

New O
occurrences O
of O
CBSD B-DISEASE
, O
confirmed O
by O
virus O
diagnostic O
tests O
, O
were O
recorded O
in O
two O
provinces O
( O
Haut B-GPE
- I-GPE
Katanga I-GPE
and O
Sud B-GPE
- I-GPE
Kivu I-GPE
) O
and O
nine O
previously O
unaffected O
territories O
, O
covering O
an O
area O
of O
> O
62,000 O
km2 O
, O
and O
at O
up O
to O
900 O
km O
from O
locations O
of O
previously O
published O
reports O
of O
CBSD B-DISEASE
in O
DRC B-GPE
. O

Banana B-DISEASE
bunchy I-DISEASE
top I-DISEASE
disease I-DISEASE
is O
one O
of O
the O
most O
serious O
diseases O
of O
bananas B-CROP
( O
Musa B-CROP
spp I-CROP
. O
) O
worldwide O
. O

The O
ITS O
, O
TEF1 O
- O
α O
, O
and O
B O
- O
tub O
sequences O
of O
the O
isolates O
showed O
100 O
% O
sequence O
similarity O
with O
Fusarium B-PATHOGEN
proliferatum I-PATHOGEN
isolates O
( O
accessions O
no O
. O

The O
results O
of O
this O
study O
confirmed O
earlier O
reports O
suggesting O
that O
sweetpotato B-CROP
leaves B-PLANT_PART
can O
be O
a O
good O
source O
of O
multiple O
WSV O
in O
the O
human O
diet O
. O

The O
disease O
was O
not O
observed O
at O
the O
only O
other O
large O
planting O
of O
banana B-CROP
on O
the O
island O
( O
26.6 B-LOC
° I-LOC
N I-LOC
, I-LOC
78.6 I-LOC
° I-LOC
W I-LOC
) O
. O

al O
. O

A O
certification O
system O
for O
seed B-PLANT_PART
potatoes B-CROP
does O
not O
exist O
in O
the O
country O
. O

The O
suspension O
was O
diluted O
1000 O
times O
with O
sterilized O
water，then O
plated O
on O
nutrient O
- O
agar O
medium O
and O
incubated O
at O
28 O
℃ O
in O
darkness O
for O
24 B-DATE
h. I-DATE
Among O
the O
32 O
isolates O
, O
23 O
pure O
bacterial O
cultures O
with O
similar O
morphology O
were O
predominantly O
obtained O
from O
the O
samples O
. O

The O
AA O
content O
in O
the O
cortex O
and O
pith O
tissue O
at O
the O
proximal O
, O
distal O
, O
and O
center O
of O
the O
root B-PLANT_PART
was O
generally O
similar O
. O

al O
. O
, O
2001 B-DATE
) O
. O

Banana B-PATHOGEN
bunchy I-PATHOGEN
top I-PATHOGEN
virus I-PATHOGEN
( O
BBTV B-PATHOGEN
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
world O
’s O
invasive O
species O
. O

( O
1 O
% O
of O
fungi O
observed O
) O
, O
Botryodiplodia B-PATHOGEN
theobromae I-PATHOGEN
Pat O
( O
7.7 O
% O
) O
, O
Fusarium B-PATHOGEN
spp I-PATHOGEN
. O

( O
3 O
) O
L. O
W. O
Liefting O
et O

Infected O
root B-PLANT_PART
and O
stem B-PLANT_PART
portions O
( O
0.5 O
to O
1 O
cm O
) O
were O
cut O
out O
, O
surface O
disinfested O
( O
10 B-DATE
min I-DATE
) O
in O
10 O
% O
bleach O
( O
0.6 O
% O
sodium O
hypochlorite O
) O
, O
rinsed O
in O
sterilized O
distilled O
water O
, O
and O
cultured O
on O
potato O
dextrose O
agar O
acidified O
to O
pH O
4.5 O
with O
0.4 O
% O
( O
vol O
/ O
vol O
) O
lactic O
acid O
. O

et O

However O
, O
this O
production O
remains O
threatened O
by O
early B-DISEASE
blight I-DISEASE
disease I-DISEASE
caused O
by O
Alternaria B-PATHOGEN
species I-PATHOGEN
including O
A. B-PATHOGEN
solani I-PATHOGEN
, O
A. B-PATHOGEN
grandis I-PATHOGEN
, O
and O
A. B-PATHOGEN
protenta I-PATHOGEN
( O
Ayad O
et O
al O
. O
2017 B-DATE
; O
Bessadat O
et O
al O
. O
2017 B-DATE
) O
. O

Bacteriol O
. O

Value O
of O
N0 O
, O
k O
and O
Ea O
were O
reported O
400 O
1156 O
mg O
/ O
kg O
, O
0.0056 O
0.098 O
per B-DATE
week I-DATE
and O
10166 O
31478 O
J O
mol O
-1 O

Pages O
37 O
- O
79 O
in O
: O
Diseases O
of O
Banana B-CROP
, O
Abacá B-CROP
and O
Enset B-CROP
. O

Samples O
were O
tested O
for O
the O
presence O
of O
BSV B-PATHOGEN
by O
two O
separate O
PCR O
amplification O
methods O
. O

Grand O
Naine O
in O
2 O
liters O
of O
spore O
suspension O
( O
1.0 O
× O
106 O
spores O
/ O
ml O
) O
. O

Cyanide O
plays O
important O
role O
in O
the O
protection O
of O
cassava B-CROP
plants O
from O
attacks O
by O
animals O
and O
insect O
pests O
. O

Mol O
. O

increasing O
root B-PLANT_PART
biomass O
( O
Partida O
et O
al O
. O
, O
2007 B-DATE
) O
, O
and O
reducing O
shoot B-PLANT_PART
elongation O
( O
Rademacher O
, O
2015 B-DATE
) O
, O
among O
others O
. O

The O
diagnosis O
was O
confirmed O
by O
real O
- O
time O
PCR O
targeting O
M. B-PATHOGEN
fijiensis I-PATHOGEN
- O
specific O
regions O
within O
the O
β O
- O
tubulin O
gene O
( O
1 O
) O
. O

Symptoms O
suggestive O
of O
phytoplasma B-DISEASE
diseases I-DISEASE
were O
observed O
in O
infected O
plantain B-CROP
plants O
in O
Serbia B-GPE
. O

In O
the O
phylogenetic O
tree O
, O
the O
present O
isolate O
was O
placed O
within O
a O
clade O
comprising O
references O
isolates O
of O
R. B-PATHOGEN
oryzae I-PATHOGEN
( O
Fig O
. O
2 O
) O
. O

cDNA O
clones O
encoding O
the O
enzymes O
involved O
in O
anthocyanin O
biosynthesis O
, O
chalcone O
synthase O
( O
CHS O
) O
, O
flavanone O
3 O
- O
hydroxylase O
( O
F3H O
) O
, O
dihydroflavonol O
4 O
- O
reductase O
( O
DRF O
) O
, O
and O
UDP O
- O
glucose O
: O
flavonoid O
3 O
- O
0- O
glucosyltransferase O
( O
3GT O
) O
, O
were O
isolated O
from O
Solanum B-CROP
pinnatisectum I-CROP
by O
RT O
- O
PCR O
with O
degenerated O
primers O
. O

Banana B-CROP
is O
one O
of O
the O
most O
consumed O
fruits B-PLANT_PART
and O
also O
a O
staple O
in O
many O
countries O
. O

Pairwise O
comparisons O
showed O
' O
Heart O
- O
o O
- O
Gold O
' O
had O
the O
highest O
sucrose O
content O
among O
the O
cultivars O
. O

In O
each O
of O
the O
districts O
, O
one O
mother O
trial O
was O
planted O
under O
irrigation O
while O
the O
other O
was O
rain O
- O
fed O
. O

Potato B-CROP
( O
Solanum B-CROP
tuberosum I-CROP
) O
is O
the O
second O
most O
important O
food O
crop O
in O
Kenya B-GPE
after O
maize B-CROP
( O
MOA B-ORG
, O
2007 B-DATE
) O
. O

In O
2008 B-DATE
and I-DATE
2009 I-DATE
, O
293 O
Streptomyces B-PATHOGEN
isolates I-PATHOGEN
were O
collected O
in O
Germany B-GPE
and O
analysed O
for O
morphology O
, O
pathogenicity O
and O
strain O
type O
. O

In O
the B-DATE
summer I-DATE
of I-DATE
1986 I-DATE
, O
a O
red O
- O
body O
mutant O
male O
beetle O
was O
found O
in O
a O
potato B-CROP
field O
on O
the O
grounds O
of O
the O
Research O
Station O
in O
Fredericton B-GPE
, O
N.B. B-GPE
, O
Canada B-GPE
. O

PCR O
products O
of O
the O
Ecuadorian B-GPE
isolate O
, O
amplified O
by O
the O
different O
CP O
primers O
described O
above O
, O
were O
assembled O
into O
a O
408 O
- O
bp O
fragment O
and O
deposited O
in O
the O
NCBI B-ORG
GenBank B-ORG
( O
KC247746 O
) O
. O

Finally O
, O
high O
number O
of O
viable O
dermal O
fibroblasts O
was O
observed O
by O
indirect O
cytotoxicity O
assay O
suggesting O
potential O
application O
of O
these O
membranes O
as O
skin O
wound O
dressing O
. O

The O
sexual O
cycle O
of O
the O
pathogen O
allows O
the O
generation O
of O
recombinant O
genotypes O
that O
can O
be O
more O
pathogenic O
or O
even O
resistant O
to O
chemicals O
. O

Despite O
the O
advances O
, O
the O
FuBC B-PATHOGEN
– O
banana B-CROP
pathosystem O
lacks O
a O
genetic O
basis O
and O
comparative O
analyses O
with O
other O
formae O
speciales O
might O
therefore O
be O
very O
useful O
as O
well O
as O
genetic O
studies O
in O
the O
host O
. O

As O
such O
, O
conventional O
plant O
breeding O
did O
not O
consider O
farmers O
’ O
preferences O
and O
attributes O
, O
locally O
available O
germplasm O
, O
and O
the O
real O
conditions O
of O
small O
- O
scale O
farmers O
in O
pursuit O
of O
developing O
crop O
cultivars O
for O
broad O
adaptation O
( O
Ceccarelli O
et O
al O
. O
, O
2000 B-DATE
; O
Witcombe O
et O
al O
. O
, O
1996 B-DATE
) O
. O

Corynespora B-PATHOGEN
cassiicola I-PATHOGEN
. O

Plants O
infected O
at O
early O
growth O
stages O
are O
severely O
dwarfed O
and O
do O
not O
bear O
fruit B-PLANT_PART
. O

Fructose O
content O
profiles O
varied O
among O
and O
within O
cultivars O
. O

al O
. O

para O
el O
primer O
ciclo O
y O
Fe O
> O
Cu O
> O
Mn≥Zn O
> O
B O
para O
el O
segundo O
ciclo O
. O

9:273 O
, O
1984 B-DATE
. O

Isolates O
of O
Rhizoctonia B-PATHOGEN
collected O
from O
the O
stems B-PLANT_PART
, O
roots B-PLANT_PART
, O
tuber B-PLANT_PART
sclerotia O
and O
soil O
of O
potato B-CROP
crops O
in O
Virginia B-GPE
and O
Lenswood B-GPE
, O
South B-GPE
Australia I-GPE
, O
were O
identified O
to O
anastomosis O
groups O
( O
AG O
) O
. O

An O
identification O
manual O
. O

Fe O
was O
the O
major O
micronutrient O
extracted O
by O
the O
corm B-PLANT_PART
, O
pseudostem B-PLANT_PART
, O
and O
bunch B-PLANT_PART
. O

Incidence O
varied O
from O
4%-60 O
% O
. O

Zebra B-DISEASE
Chip I-DISEASE
( O
ZC B-DISEASE
) O
, O
an O
emerging O
disease O
of O
potato B-CROP
( O
Solanum B-CROP
tuberosum I-CROP
L. O
) O
first O
documented O
in O
potato B-CROP
fields O
around O
Saltillo B-GPE
in O
México B-GPE
in O
1994 B-DATE
, O
has O
been O
identified O
in O
the O
southwestern B-LOC
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
, O
México B-GPE
, O
and O
Central B-LOC
America I-LOC
and O
is O
causing O
losses O
of O
millions O
of O
dollars O
to O
the O
potato B-CROP
industry O
( O
4 O
) O
. O

Phytopathology O
94:163 O
, O
2004 B-DATE
. O

( O
2 O
) O
studied O
a O
broad O
population O
of O
27 O
isolates O
from O
potato B-CROP
crops O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Michoacán B-GPE
( O
Mx B-GPE
) O
, O
and O
found O
two O
homothallic O
isolates O
among O
heterothallic O
isolates O
; O
the O
ratio O
was O
1:1 O
. O

Well O
- O
developed O
conidia O
were O
long O
- O
obclavate O
, O
obtuse O
at O
both O
ends O
, O
straight O
, O
brown O
, O
with O
five O
to O
eight O
transverse O
septa O
, O
and O
measured O
49.7 O
to O
117.1 O
× O
13.3 O
to O
17.2 O
μm O
. O

Phylogenetic O
studies O
have O
shown O
the O
existence O
of O
distinct O
genetic O
lineages O
for O
Foc B-PATHOGEN
, O
which O
has O
come O
to O
be O
called O
the O
Fusarium B-PATHOGEN
oxysporum I-PATHOGEN
Species I-PATHOGEN
Complex I-PATHOGEN
( O
FOSC B-PATHOGEN
) O
( O
O'Donnell O
et O
al O
. O

42:26 O
, O
1993 B-DATE
. O

Based O
on O
morphology O
, O
the O
pathogen O
was O
identified O
as O
Alternaria B-PATHOGEN
longipes I-PATHOGEN
( O
1 O
) O
. O

The O
results O
were O
also O
supported O
by O
variation O
in O
gene O
expression O
analysis O
of O
cuticular O
wax O
biosynthetic O
genes O
- O
FATB O
and O
KCS11 O
. O

This O
is O
the O
first O
report O
of O
M. B-PATHOGEN
phaseolina I-PATHOGEN
causing O
pre O
- O
harvest O
cassava B-DISEASE
root I-DISEASE
rot I-DISEASE
in O
Benin B-GPE
and O
Nigeria B-GPE
. O

Surveys O
were O
undertaken O
for O
tracing O
the O
cassava O
mealybug O
infestation O
at O
multiple O
locations O
in O
Namakkal B-GPE
and O
Salem B-GPE
districts O
of O
Tamil B-GPE
Nadu I-GPE
, O
India B-GPE
. O

For O
approximately B-DATE
70 I-DATE
years I-DATE
, O
CBSD B-DISEASE
was O
restricted O
to O
coastal B-LOC
East I-LOC
Africa I-LOC
and O
so O
had O
a O
relatively O
low O
impact O
on O
food O
security O
compared O
with O
CMD B-DISEASE
. O

Greenhouse O
and O
ﬁeld O
culture O
systems O
were O
used O
to O
study O
the O
effect O
of O
drought O
conditions O
on O
the O
storage O
root B-PLANT_PART
( O
SR O
) O
formation O
in O
‘ O
Beauregard O
’ O
sweetpotato B-CROP
( O
Ipomoea B-CROP
batatas I-CROP
) O
. O

Mean O
incidence O
differed O
significantly O
between O
districts O
and O
between O
counties O
within O
some O
districts O
. O

Both O
of O
the O
infected O
fields O
were O
placed O
under O
quarantine O
, O
and O
symptomatic O
plants O
were O
destroyed O
. O

The O
inoculation O
of O
three O
isolates O
was O
carried O
out O
in O
three O
plants O
, O
three O
leaves B-PLANT_PART
for O
each O
plant O
, O
by O
spraying O
spore O
solution O
with O
a O
concentration O
of O
1×106 O
conidia O
/ O
ml O
, O
without O
wounding O
the O
leaves B-PLANT_PART
and O
placed O
in O
a O
humid O
chamber O
at O
25 O
° O
C O
for O
ten B-DATE
days I-DATE
. O

B. O
Sutton O
& O
Dyko O
( O
56.2 O
% O
) O
, O
Penicillium B-PATHOGEN
spp I-PATHOGEN
. O

Fusarium B-PATHOGEN
oxysporum I-PATHOGEN
was O
re O
