AF520707 O
) O
, O
and O
98 O
% O
identical O
to O
that O
of O
type O
strain O
CFBP O
1200 O
T O
of O
D. B-PATHOGEN
dianthicola I-PATHOGEN
( O
Accession O
No O
. O

) O
was O
first O
fully O
characterized O
in O
the O
U.S. B-GPE
in O
1977 B-DATE
( O
2 O
) O
. O

Verhoeven O
et O
al O
. O

Leaves B-PLANT_PART
from O
10 O
symptomatic O
and O
three O
symptomless O
plants O
were O
sampled O
from O
each O
field O
and O
tested O
by O
double O
antibody O
sandwich O
( O
DAS)-ELISA O
( O
1 O
) O
at O
ARI O
- O
Uyole O
. O

Sweepovirus(es B-PATHOGEN
) I-PATHOGEN
was O
detected O
frequently O
using O
generic O
primers O
in O
cultivars O
Ejumula O
, O
New O
Kawogo O
and O
318L O
in O
eastern B-LOC
and I-LOC
central I-LOC
Uganda I-LOC
. O

SPW O
quarantine O
has O
effectively O
reduced O
detections O
in O
Alabama B-GPE
. O

 O
. O

Page O
315 O
in O
: O
PCR O
Protocols O
: O
A O
Guide O
to O
Methods O
and O
Applications O
. O

Sutton O
& O
Dyko O
( O
56.2 O
% O
) O
, O
Penicillium B-PATHOGEN
spp I-PATHOGEN
. O

) O
Phytopathology O
101(suppl.):S162 O
, O
2011 B-DATE
. O

Grünwald O
et O
al O
. O

The O
average O
ID O
and O
frequency O
distributions O
within O
S O
1 O
families O
for O
different O
traits O
correlated O
well O
with O
the O
relative O
importance O
of O
nonadditive O
genetic O
effects O
controlling O
their O
inheritance O
as O
reported O
in O
the O
literature O
. O

Degenerate O
primers O
SPG1 O
/ O
SPG2 O
, O
developed O
for O
PCR O
detection O
of O
begomoviruses O
( O
1 O
) O
, O
amplified O
a O
912 O
- O
bp O
DNA O
fragment O
from O
3 O
of O
10 O
DNA O
extracts O
from O
I. B-CROP
setosa I-CROP
and O
5 O
of O
39 O
sweetpotato B-CROP
plants O
held O
in O
quarantine O
. O

( O
1 O
) O
infecting O
cassava B-CROP
in O
Colombia B-GPE
. O

The O
objective O
of O
this O
study O
was O
to O
determine O
the O
ascorbic O
acid O
( O
AA O
) O
, O
thiamin O
( O
B1 O
) O
, O
riboflavin O
( O
B2 O
) O
, O
and O
vitamin O
B6 O
content O
in O
a O
range O
of O
foliar O
tissues O
including O
buds B-PLANT_PART
, O
vines B-PLANT_PART
, O
young O
petioles B-PLANT_PART
, O
young O
leaves B-PLANT_PART
, O
mature O
petioles B-PLANT_PART
, O
and O
mature O
leaves B-PLANT_PART
and O
root B-PLANT_PART
tissues O
including O
the O
skin O
, O
cortex O
, O
and O
pith O
tissue O
at O
the O
proximal O
, O
distal O
, O
and O
center O
regions O
of O
the O
root B-PLANT_PART
. O

In O
this O
paper O
, O
we O
report O
phylogenetic O
relationships O
, O
rates O
of O
synonymous O
and O
non O
- O
synonymous O
substitutions O
, O
and O
whole O
genome O
- O
based O
evolutionary O
rates O
for O
CBSV B-PATHOGEN
and O
UCBSV B-PATHOGEN
. O

Fungal O
Diversity O
39:89 O
, O
2009 B-DATE
. O

EU834131 O
and O
EU935005 O
) O
. O

Page O
59 O
in O
: O
Mycosphaerella B-DISEASE
Leaf I-DISEASE
Spot I-DISEASE
Disease I-DISEASE
of O
Bananas B-CROP
: O
Present O
Status O
and O
Outlook O
. O

After O
harvest O
and O
evaluation O
of O
the O
agronomic O
trials O
, O
storage O
evaluation O
of O
potato B-CROP
tuberworm O
damage O
was O
done O
at O
the O
CIP O
Research O
Station O
. O

J. O

Total O
DNA O
was O
extracted O
from O
90 O
leaf B-PLANT_PART
samples O
randomly O
collected O
from O
symptomatic O
and O
asymptomatic O
banana B-CROP
and O
plantain B-CROP
plants O
in O
these O
areas O
. O

Appresoria O
were O
ovate O
to O
obovate O
, O
dark O
brown O
, O
and O
9 O
to O
15 O
× O
7 O
to O
12 O
μm O
and O
setae O
were O
present O
, O
slightly O
swollen O
at O
the O
base O
, O
with O
a O
tapered O
apex O
, O
and O
brown O
. O

AA O
also O
has O
antioxidant O
properties O
that O
may O
protect O
the O
human O
body O
against O
reactive O
oxygen O
species O
( O
Padayatty O
et O
al O
. O

Gevens O
. O

Tubers B-PLANT_PART
of O
potato B-CROP
cv O
. O

Observations O
associated O
the O
symptoms O
with O
thrips O
feeding O
damage O
so O
plants O
were O
tested O
for O
Tomato B-PATHOGEN
spotted I-PATHOGEN
wilt I-PATHOGEN
virus I-PATHOGEN
( O
TSWV B-PATHOGEN
) O
and O
Impatiens B-PATHOGEN
necrotic I-PATHOGEN
spot I-PATHOGEN
virus I-PATHOGEN
( O
INSV B-PATHOGEN
) O
with O
ImmunoStrips O
from O
Agdia B-ORG
, O
Inc B-GPE
( O
Elkhart B-GPE
, O
IN B-GPE
) O
. O

Twenty O
- O
two O
pure O
cultures O
were O
induced O
to O
sporulate O
by O
plating O
on O
V8 O
medium O
and O
incubating O
for O
2 B-DATE
weeks I-DATE
under O
alternating O
12 B-DATE
- I-DATE
h I-DATE
darkness O
and O
12 B-DATE
- I-DATE
h I-DATE
near O
- O
ultraviolet O
light O
. O

, O
EF044304 O
, O
X52037 O
, O
and O
Y09577 O
) O
. O

Further O
testing O
confirmed O
the O
presence O
of O
BBrMV B-PATHOGEN
in O
symptomatic O
plants O
from O
four O
different O
provinces O
. O

The O
resistance O
mechanism O
was O
limited O
to O
within O
a O
chemical O
family O
( O
phenoxycarboxylic O
acid O
) O
and O
did O
not O
occur O
across O
all O
WSSA O
Group O
4 O
synthetic O
auxin O
herbicides O
, O
as O
the O
pyridinecarboxylic O
acid O
herbicides O
clopyralid O
and O
triclopyr O
and O
the O
arylpicolinate O
herbicide O
halauxifen O
- O
methyl O
provided O
control O
in O
our O
experiments O
. O

, O
were O
collected O
in O
the O
municipality O
of O
Ponte B-GPE
Nova I-GPE
, O
Minas B-GPE
Gerais I-GPE
, O
Brazil B-GPE
( O
20 B-LOC
° I-LOC
24 I-LOC
’ I-LOC
39 I-LOC
” I-LOC
S I-LOC
and I-LOC
42 I-LOC
° I-LOC
55 I-LOC
’ I-LOC
15 I-LOC
” I-LOC
W I-LOC
; I-LOC
456 I-LOC
m I-LOC
) O
in O
July B-DATE
, I-DATE
2011 I-DATE
. O

Ten O
plants O
per O
isolate O
were O
inoculated O
by O
submerging O
their O
roots B-PLANT_PART
in O
a O
suspension O
of O
microconidia O
( O
105 O
spores O
/ O
ml O
) O
. O

There O
was O
variability O
among O
strains O
for O
shape O
( O
form O
) O
, O
contour O
( O
margin O
) O
and O
elevation O
. O

in O
Taiwan B-GPE
. O

We O
have O
reported O
the O
first O
cassava B-CROP
- O
infected O
geminivirus O
- O
Sri B-PATHOGEN
Lankan I-PATHOGEN
cassava I-PATHOGEN
mosaic I-PATHOGEN
virus I-PATHOGEN
( O
SLCMV B-PATHOGEN
- I-PATHOGEN
HN7 I-PATHOGEN
strain O
) O
in O
China B-GPE
. O

Fonsah O
et O
al O
. O

PVX B-PATHOGEN
and O
PVM B-PATHOGEN
were O
found O
in O
most O
fields O
and O
in O
14 O
% O
and O
5 O
% O
of O
the O
samples O
, O
respectively O
. O

( O
1 O
% O
of O
fungi O
observed O
) O
, O
Botryodiplodia B-PATHOGEN
theobromae I-PATHOGEN
Pat O
( O
7.7 O
% O
) O
, O
Fusarium B-PATHOGEN
spp I-PATHOGEN
. O

To O
the O
best O
of O
our O
knowledge O
, O
Clostridium O
sensu O
stricto O
cluster O
1 O
and O
Lysinibacillus O
in O
fufu O
, O
and O
Brevundimonas O
, O
Cupriavidus O
, O
Sphingomonas O
and O
Strenotrophomomas O
in O
garri O
are O
reported O
for O
the O
first O
time O
. O

Cassava B-PATHOGEN
begomoviruses I-PATHOGEN
severely O
constrain O
cassava B-CROP
production O
in O
Africa B-LOC
. O

In O
addition O
to O
the O
necrotic O
lesions O
on O
leaves B-PLANT_PART
observed O
in O
cv O
. O

In O
Italy B-GPE
, O
some O
of O
these O
species O
and O
hybrids O
are O
grown O
as O
ornamental O
evergreen O
vines O
or O
shrubs O
. O

Furthermore O
, O
the O
obtained O
CP O
gene O
sequence O
( O
MN567072 O
) O
also O
showed O
100 O
% O
identity O
with O
BSV B-PATHOGEN
isolate O
BSOLV O
- O
IN2 O
. O

Thus O
, O
it O
is O
necessary O
and O
worthwhile O
to O
identify O
resistance O
loci O
to O
help O
develop O
disease O
- O
resistant O
varieties O
. O

The O
low O
incidence O
of O
the O
virus O
( O
11.43 O
% O
; O
4 O
of O
35 O
samples O
) O
suggests O
that O
CsVX B-PATHOGEN
has O
been O
introduced O
only O
recently O
via O
infected O
planting O
stock O
. O

Atlantic O
) O
plants O
, O
20 O
to O
25 O
cm O
high O
, O
grown O
from O
prenuclear O
minitubers O
in O
greenhouses O
located O
at O
the O
USDA B-ORG
- I-ORG
ARS I-ORG
facility O
in O
Prosser B-GPE
, O
WA B-GPE
exhibited O
necrotic O
spots O
similar O
to O
those O
produced O
by O
the O
early B-DISEASE
blight I-DISEASE
pathogen O
, O
Alternaria B-PATHOGEN
solani I-PATHOGEN
. O

, O
2008 B-DATE
) O
. O

In O
root B-PLANT_PART
tissues O
of O
‘ O
Beauregard O
’ O
and O
‘ O
LA O
07 O
- O
146 O
’ O
sweetpotatoes B-CROP
, O
the O
AA O
content O
was O
lower O
in O
the O
skin O
( O
1.9 O
to O
5.6 O
mg O
and O
2.54 O
to O
3.82 O
mg O
, O
respectively O
) O
. O

In O
the O
new O
spread O
zone O
of O
Haut B-GPE
- I-GPE
Katanga I-GPE
, O
incidence O
increased O
from O
1.7 O
% O
to O
15.9 O
% O
. O

Potato B-CROP
( O
Solanum B-CROP
tuberosum I-CROP
L. O

based O
on O
the O
dark O
, O
brown O
, O
obclavate O
to O
obpyriform O
catenulate O
conidia O
with O
longitudinal O
and O
transverse O
septa O
tapering O
to O
a O
prominent O
beak O
attached O
in O
chains O
on O
a O
simple O
and O
short O
conidiophore O
( O
2 O
) O
. O

Data O
were O
collected O
through O
a O
participatory O
rural O
appraisal O
( O
PRA O
) O
methodology O
using O
a O
semistructured O
questionnaire O
and O
focus O
group O
discussions O
. O

Seedlings O
were O
inoculated O
by O
wounding O
the O
roots B-PLANT_PART
and O
depositing O
a O
suspension O
of O
conidia O
and O
chlamydospores O
at O
105 O
spores O
mL-1 O
. O

Symptoms O
ofFusariumwilt B-DISEASE
, O
including O
wilting O
of O
leaves B-PLANT_PART
and O
vascular O
discoloration O
in O
rhizomes B-PLANT_PART
and O
pseudostems B-PLANT_PART
, O
were O
first O
observed O
in O
2012 B-DATE
in O
a O
2 O
- O
ha O
Cavendish B-CROP
plantation O
in O
Baoo B-LOC
Pooran I-LOC
( O
ca O
. O

E. O

The O
information O
related O
to O
the O
etiological O
agent O
of O
this O
disease O
is O
contradictory O
, O
because O
some O
authors O
believe O
it O
is O
caused O
by O
phytoplasmas O
while O
others O
believe O
that O
it O
is O
caused O
by O
a O
virus O
. O

Two O
viroids O
belonging O
to O
the O
family O
Pospiviroidae O
, O
Potato B-PATHOGEN
spindle I-PATHOGEN
tuber I-PATHOGEN
viroid I-PATHOGEN
( O
PSTVd B-PATHOGEN
) O
and O
Dahlia B-PATHOGEN
latent I-PATHOGEN
viroid I-PATHOGEN
( O
DLVd B-PATHOGEN
) O
, O
were O
identified O
separately O
from O
dahlia B-CROP
plants O
in O
Japan B-GPE
and O
… O

( O
2 O
) O
R. O

Fungal O
colonies O
were O
initially O
white O
, O
turned O
brown O
with O
age O
, O
and O
produced O
irregularly O
shaped O
, O
brown O
sclerotia O
. O

The O
software O
used O
for O
HPLC O
programming O
and O
data O
collection O
was O
Waters O
Empower O
3 O
. O

95:447 O
, O
2013 B-DATE
. O

) O
Phytopathology O
100 O
: O
S161 O
, O
2010 B-DATE
. O

It O
has O
been O
recorded O
to O
be O
causing O
major O
damage O
to O
a O
range O
of O
economically O
important O
crops O
and O
is O
increasingly O
recorded O
from O
new O
locations O
. O

, O
2018 B-DATE
) O
. O

SPFMV B-PATHOGEN
— I-PATHOGEN
strain I-PATHOGEN
O I-PATHOGEN
( O
SPFMV B-PATHOGEN
- I-PATHOGEN
O I-PATHOGEN
) O
was O
detected O
in O
a O
plant O
grown O
from O
a O
sweet B-CROP
potato I-CROP
sample O
from O
the B-LOC
East I-LOC
Kimberley I-LOC
region O
of O
Western B-LOC
Australia I-LOC
. O

For O
polymerase O
chain O
reaction O
( O
PCR O
) O
, O
the O
upstream O
primer O
No O
. O

24 B-LOC
° I-LOC
N I-LOC
, I-LOC
68 I-LOC
° I-LOC
E I-LOC
) O
, O
Sindh B-GPE
Province I-GPE
. O

The O
present O
study O
was O
undertaken O
to O
document O
these O
carbohydrate O
- O
related O
changes O
in O
six O
sweetpotato B-CROP
cul O
tivars O
. O

Moyer O
. O

15 O
No O
. O

Seidl O
and O
A. O

( O
3 O
) O
N. O

The O
biochemical O
analyses O
performed O
on O
young O
and O
old O
tubers B-PLANT_PART
after O
high O
- O
temperature O
treatment O
( O
65 O
degrees O
C O
) O
revealed O
an O
increase O
in O
the O
formation O
rate O
of O
fructose O
and O
glucose O
by O
a O
factor O
of O
16.4 O
and O
5 O
. O

Measurements O
from O
four O
replicate O
petri O
dishes O
per O
concentration O
of O
fludioxonil O
were O
taken O
. O

Cyanogenic O
glycosides O
, O
linamarin O
and O
lotaustralin O
, O
are O
presents O
in O
all O
tissues O
of O
Cassava B-PATHOGEN
( O
Manihot B-CROP
esculenta I-CROP
Crantz O
) O
except O
seeds B-PLANT_PART
and O
function O
as O
a O
deterrent O
for O
herbivores O
as O
well O
as O
the O
translocable O
form O
of O
reduced O
nitrogen O
. O

The O
spatial O
 O
expression O
analysis O
indicated O
that O
these O
genes O
were O
preferentially O
expressed O
in O
flowers B-PLANT_PART
, O
stolons B-PLANT_PART
and O
 O
terminal O
buds B-PLANT_PART
, O
and O
their O
transcripts O
could O
not O
detected O
in O
roots B-PLANT_PART
except O
3GT O
. O

( O
4 O
) O
K. O

Fungicide O
sprays O
did O
not O
reduce O
incidence O
of O
the O
symptoms O
. O

At O
the B-ORG
International I-ORG
Centre I-ORG
for I-ORG
Diarrhoeal I-ORG
Disease I-ORG
Research I-ORG
, O
Bangladesh B-GPE
( O
icddr B-ORG
, I-ORG
b I-ORG
) O
, O
for O
the B-DATE
last I-DATE
two I-DATE
decades I-DATE
, O
a O
consensus O
- O
based O
guideline O
has O
been O
followed O
for O
PD O
. O

Rep. O

Symptoms O
were O
observed O
before O
early B-DISEASE
blight I-DISEASE
, O
from O
50 B-DATE
to I-DATE
60 I-DATE
days I-DATE
after O
emergence O
of O
the O
potato B-CROP
plants O
. O

AG-4 O
isolates O
produced O
the O
most O
severe O
stem B-PLANT_PART
and O
stolon B-PLANT_PART
cankers O
of O
all O
isolates O
tested O
. O

Two O
sectors O
in O
each O
district O
were O
sampled O
. O

Sequence O
analysis O
revealed O
that O
the O
obtained O
partial O
sequence O
of O
the O
AP O
and O
RT O
region O
( O
MN567071 O
) O
shared O
100 O
% O
identity O
to O
corresponding O
sequences O
from O
BSV B-ORG
OL I-ORG
virus O
isolate O
BSOLV O
- O
IN2 O
( O
accession O
no O
. O

We O
report O
optical O
, O
X O
- O
ray O
, O
polarization O
and O
response O
time O
measurements O
on O
a O
new O
bananas O
- O
haped O
mesogen O
. O

In O
Caldas B-GPE
, O
losses O
from O
dumping O
have O
reached O
70 O
% O
( O
Guzmán O
et O
al O
. O

( O
3 O
) O
, O
who O
conducted O
a O
study O
with O
isolates O
collected O
from O
the O
Toluca B-GPE
Valley I-GPE
region O
in O
1997 B-DATE
and I-DATE
1998 I-DATE
, O
finding O
a O
1:1 O
frequency O
between O
compatibility O
types O
A1 O
and O
A2 O
. O

However O
, O
99 O
% O
identity O
was O
observed O
when O
PCR O
products O
from O
the O
Ecuadorian B-GPE
isolate O
were O
compared O
with O
the O
corresponding O
fragment O
of O
a O
BBrMV B-PATHOGEN
isolate O
from O
the O
Philippines B-GPE
( O
NCBI B-ORG
Accession O
No O
. O

Epidemiological O
investigations O
were O
conducted O
during O
May B-DATE
2012 I-DATE
at O
31 O
locations O
in O
Ogun B-GPE
State I-GPE
to O
determine O
the O
potential O
risk O
of O
BBTV B-PATHOGEN
spreading O
into O
Nigeria B-GPE
. O

Results O
indicated O
that O
the O
phytoplasma O
, O
here O
identified O
in O
association O
with O
potato B-CROP
plants O
, O
shared O
best O
sequence O
identity O
( O
99 O
% O
) O
with O
members O
of O
subgroup O
16SrXII B-PATHOGEN
- I-PATHOGEN
A I-PATHOGEN
( O
e.g. O

The O
need O
to O
do O
extensive O
surveys O
for O
the O
presence O
of O
BBTV B-PATHOGEN
in O
other O
banana B-CROP
production O
regions O
in O
South B-GPE
Africa I-GPE
is O
highlighted O
by O
this O
finding O
. O

The O
study O
described O
here O
, O
comprises O
the O
first O
extensive O
assessment O
of O
temporal O
change O
in O
occurrence O
of O
CBSD B-DISEASE
and O
its O
causal O
viruses O
in O
DRC B-GPE
, O
based O
on O
surveys O
conducted O
during O
2016 B-DATE
and I-DATE
2018 I-DATE
. O

AJ964960 O
) O
. O

The O
plant O
is O
native O
to O
the O
southwestern B-LOC
China I-LOC
, O
where O
it O
grows O
semi O
- O
wild O
in O
the O
mountains O
between O
1,500 O
and O
2,500 O
m O
above O
sea O
level O
. O

The O
data O
from O
this O
study O
show O
that O
diversity O
among O
scab B-PATHOGEN
- I-PATHOGEN
causing I-PATHOGEN
species I-PATHOGEN
in O
Germany B-GPE
is O
much O
higher O
than O
previously O
thought O
. O

Q. O

In O
2010 B-DATE
, O
three O
US-23 O
isolates O
were O
recovered O
from O
three O
locations O
( O
two O
counties O
) O
, O
out O
of O
20 O
fields O
tested O
. O

, O
2012 B-DATE
) O
. O

The O
samples O
were O
indexed O
for O
BSV B-PATHOGEN
and O
CMV B-PATHOGEN
by O
both O
triple O
antibody O
sandwich O
indirect O
enzyme O
- O
linked O
immunosorbent O
assay O
( O
TAS O
- O
ELISA O
) O
and O
immunosorbent O
electron O
microscopy O
( O
ISEM O
) O
to O
ascertain O
the O
presence O
of O
these O
two O
viruses O
. O

Two O
of O
the O
samples O
collected O
from O
the O
western B-LOC
region I-LOC
of O
Ghana B-GPE
produced O
strong O
reactions O
with O
MAb O
SCR23 O
but O
did O
not O
react O
with O
ACMV B-PATHOGEN
- O
specific O
MAb O
SCR O
33 O
. O

References O
: O
( O
1 O
) O
K. O

, O
2010 B-DATE
; O
Wong O
et O
al O
. O

The O
fungus O
produced O
abundant O
macroconidia O
in O
spezieller O
nährstoffarmer O
agar O
( O
SNA O
) O
culture O
medium O
containing O
clove O
leaf O
( O
CLA O
) O
after O
14 B-DATE
days I-DATE
of O
incubation O
at O
25 O
° O
C O
. O

W. O

2 O
) O
. O

( O
2.4 O
% O
) O
. O

55 O
% O
) O
. O

L. O

FJ852715 O
, O
EF198117 O
, O
and O
AY238606 O
) O
of O
C. B-PATHOGEN
cassiicola I-PATHOGEN
( O
1 O
) O
. O

Another O
PCR O
analysis O
was O
targeting O
the O
coat O
protein O
( O
CP O
) O
region O
of O
ORF3 O
with O
primer O
pair O
BSV O
156 O
( O
5′-TTACCTCCAGCACAAAGTCG-3′ O
) O
and O
BSV O
962 O
( O
5′-TTCTCCACAGGCATAACACC-3′ O
) O
designed O
in O
this O
study O
with O
a O
product O
size O
of O
806 O
bp O
. O

, O
2020 B-DATE
) O
and O
banana B-CROP
production O
( O
Robinson O
and O
Galán O
, O
2012 B-DATE
) O
. O

Consequently O
, O
the O
exploitation O
of O
the O
supposed O
direct O
relationship O
between O
leaf B-PLANT_PART
HCN O
and O
root B-PLANT_PART
HCN O
in O
the O
selection O
of O
low O
HCN O
clones O
in O
cassava B-CROP
breeding O
programmes O
needs O
to O
be O
carefully O
assessed O
. O

The O
906 O
- O
bp O
amplicon O
from O
one O
sample O
was O
cloned O
and O
three O
clones O
were O
sequenced O
. O

( O
2 O
) O
J. O

The O
corresponding O
mitochondrial O
gene O
has O
been O
cloned O
and O
sequenced O
. O

Phytopathol O
. O

Mycotaxon O
104:189 O
, O
2008 B-DATE
. O

Plant O
Ind. O

( O
2 O
) O
B. O

The O
Fusarium B-DISEASE
wilt I-DISEASE
incidence O
in O
cv O
. O

When O
buds B-PLANT_PART
were O
completely O
colonized O
, O
sprouting O
was O
completely O
inhibited O
. O

Pages O
23 O
- O
25 O
in O
: O
Compendium O
of O
Potato O
Diseases O
. O

A O
50 O
μl O
of O
tissue O
suspensions O
was O
streaked O
onto O
Luria B-GPE
- I-GPE
Bertani I-GPE
( O
LB O
) O
medium O
. O

Phytopathology O
87:698 O
, O
1997 B-DATE
. O

The O
log O
reduction O
results O
for O
B. O

The O
inoculation O
assay O
used O
three O
leaves B-PLANT_PART
, O
totaling O
72 O
spots O
for O
control O
and O
36 O
spots O
for O
inoculation O
. O

Originality O
/ O
valueApplication O
of O
PCN O
and O
SPI O
in O
batter O
system O
to O
develop O
banana B-CROP
fritters O
with O
low O
oil O
content O
, O
moist O
fruit B-PLANT_PART
core O
and O
crunchy O
crust O
is O
reported O
for O
the O
first O
time O
. O

Results O
suggest O
that O
rhizoctonia B-DISEASE
disease I-DISEASE
in O
potato B-CROP
fields O
in O
South B-LOC
Australia I-LOC
is O
caused O
by O
a O
combination O
of O
different O
anastomosis O
groups O
and O
this O
has O
important O
implications O
for O
crop O
rotations O
. O

( O
2 O
) O
D. O

Chimoio B-GPE
is O
the O
capital O
of O
an O
agriculturally O
rich O
highland O
province O
. O

Mordue O
. O

Samson O
et O
al O
. O

Previous O
reports O
derived O
from O
single O
samples O
recorded O
the O
presence O
of O
African B-PATHOGEN
cassava I-PATHOGEN
mosaic I-PATHOGEN
virus I-PATHOGEN
( O
ACMV B-PATHOGEN
) O
and O
East B-PATHOGEN
African I-PATHOGEN
cassava I-PATHOGEN
mosaic I-PATHOGEN
virus I-PATHOGEN
( O
EACMV B-PATHOGEN
) O
in O
Angola B-GPE
. O

Wu O
and O
H. O

Abstract O
Potato B-CROP
tuberworm O
, O
Phthorimaea O
operculella O
( O
Zeller O
) O
, O
is O
the O
most O
serious O
insect O
pest O
of O
potatoes B-CROP
worldwide O
. O

Eighteen O
cassava B-CROP
ﬁelds O
were O
sampled O
in O
Bengo B-GPE
, O
Cuanza B-GPE
Norte I-GPE
, O
Malanje B-GPE
and O
Uige B-GPE
Provinces I-GPE
. O

doi O
: O
10.1111 O
/ O
ppa.12077 O
, O
2013 B-DATE
. O

( O
2017 B-DATE
) O
. O

Song O
( O
1998 B-DATE
) O
reported O
that O
the O
end O
users O
’ O
participation O
in O
the O
improvement O
of O
seed B-PLANT_PART
systems O
led O
to O
the O
efficient O
use O
of O
national O
genetic O
resources O
and O
promoted O
their O
production O
. O

66 O
. O

Mediterr O
. O

Modelling O
showed O
that O
plantain B-CROP
and O
chicory B-CROP
need O
to O
be O
sown O
before O
mid B-DATE
- I-DATE
March I-DATE
in O
Manawatu B-GPE
to O
be O
ready O
for O
their O
first O
grazing O
before O
winter B-DATE
. O

Although O
the O
disease O
occurs O
throughout O
the O
humid O
tropics O
, O
it O
has O
been O
reported O
in O
the O
Caribbean B-LOC
from O
only O
Cuba B-GPE
, O
Hispaniola B-GPE
, O
and O
Jamaica B-GPE
( O
1 O
) O
. O

The O
predicted O
SPITI1 O
protein O
had O
168 O
, O
172 O
, O
or O
174 O
amino O
acid O
residues O
, O
and O
molecular O
weights O
ranging O
from O
17.88 O
to O
18.38 O
kDa O
. O

Thomas O
. O

CMI O
Description O
of O
Pathogenic O
Fungi O
and O
Bacteria O
, O
No O
. O

The O
reisolated O
fungi O
were O
identified O
using O
morphology O
and O
a O
subset O
was O
confirmed O
by O
sequencing O
. O

Our O
results O
have O
implications O
for O
the O
development O
of O
RNAi O
approaches O
for O
managing O
important O
crop O
pests O
, O
in O
that O
banana B-CROP
weevils O
can O
be O
controlled O
based O
on O
the O
silencing O
of O
essential O
target O
genes O
as O
snf7 O
, O
rps13 O
, O
and O
mad1 O
. O

Plates O
were O
incubated O
at O
25 O
° O
C O
overnight O
to O
allow O
conidia O
to O
germinate O
. O

Water O
- O
soluble O
vitamins O
, O
including O
AA O
and O
B O
vitamins O
, O
are O
essential O
compounds O
for O
adequate O
functioning O
of O
the O
human O
body O
. O

It O
contributes O
to O
the O
knowledge O
on O
the O
systematics O
of O
Fusarium B-PATHOGEN
species I-PATHOGEN
with O
pathogenicity O
to O
banana B-CROP
, O
their O
genotypic O
diversity O
and O
pathogenicity O
, O
as O
well O
as O
on O
non O
- O
pathogenic O
Fusarium B-PATHOGEN
spp I-PATHOGEN
. O

KY369923 O
) O
. O

In O
2001 B-DATE
, O
plants O
of O
Dominico O
- O
Hartón O
plantain B-CROP
showing O
mild B-DISEASE
chlorotic I-DISEASE
streak I-DISEASE
symptoms O
were O
observed O
in O
northwestern B-LOC
Colombia I-LOC
. O

The O
characteristics O
of O
good O
storage O
roots B-PLANT_PART
identified O
by O
farmers O
included O
high O
dry O
matter O
content O
, O
good O
culinary O
taste O
, O
good O
shape O
, O
root B-PLANT_PART
size O
, O
and O
sweetness O
representing O
27.4 O
% O
, O
18.8 O
% O
, O
16.1 O
% O
, O
11.6 O
% O
, O
and O
9.4 O
% O
, O
respectively O
. O

Cassava B-CROP
is O
consumed O
in O
the B-GPE
Democratic I-GPE
Republic I-GPE
of I-GPE
Congo I-GPE
( O
DRC B-GPE
) O
as O
a O
staple O
food O
for O
the O
majority O
of O
the O
Congolese B-GPE
population O
. O

Calculated O
EC50 O
values O
( O
fludioxonil O
concentration O
inhibiting O
pathogen O
growth O
by O
50 O
% O
) O
were O
obtained O
. O

Control O
plants O
were O
asymptomatic O
. O

( O
3 O
) O
P. O

A O
BLASTn O
search O
using O
the O
KJ806191 O
sequence O
revealed O
it O
to O
be O
99 O
% O
identical O
to O
around O
20 O
different O
strains O
of O
A. B-PATHOGEN
longipes I-PATHOGEN
deposited O
in O
GenBank B-ORG
including O
leaf B-PATHOGEN
spot I-PATHOGEN
pathogens I-PATHOGEN
of O
another O
Solanaceaeous O
member O
, O
Nicotiana B-CROP
tabacum I-CROP
( O
AY154684 O
) O
and O
Asteraceous O
plant O
, O
Atractylodes B-CROP
macrocepha I-CROP
( O
JQ004404 O
) O
. O

( O
3 O
) O
H. O

Potato B-CROP
is O
the O
fourth O
most O
important O
agricultural O
commodity O
in O
Michigan B-GPE
and O
is O
grown O
for O
table O
stock O
, O
chip O
processing O
, O
and O
seed B-PLANT_PART
. O

During O
July B-DATE
2016 I-DATE
, O
leaf B-PLANT_PART
- O
yellowing O
and O
wilting O
, O
accompanied O
by O
internal O
vascular O
discolorations O
of O
rhizomes B-PLANT_PART
and O
pseudostems B-PLANT_PART
, O
were O
observed O
in O
mature O
‘ O
Grande O
Naine O
’ O
Cavendish B-CROP
plants O
from O
Shfeya B-GPE
, O
Carmel B-GPE
coastal O
plain O
( O
32 B-LOC
° I-LOC
35′5.6″N I-LOC
; I-LOC
34 I-LOC
° I-LOC
56′27.6″E I-LOC
) O
, O
and O
2 B-DATE
months I-DATE
later I-DATE
in O
plants O
from O
Kibbutz O
Ein B-GPE
Gev I-GPE
, O
eastern B-LOC
shore I-LOC
of I-LOC
Lake I-LOC
Galilee I-LOC
( O
32 B-LOC
° I-LOC
46′29.6″N I-LOC
; I-LOC
35 I-LOC
° I-LOC
38′23.8″E I-LOC
) O
. O

The B-ORG
NC I-ORG
Extension I-ORG
Service I-ORG
initiated O
a O
multimedia O
programme O
on O
SPW O
. O

( O
4 O
) O
Y. O

2019 B-DATE
) O
. O

Trop O
. O

Loria O
, O
G. O

The O
biggest O
decrease O
in O
the O
cultivation O
of O
Ebwanateraka O
had O
occurred O
in O
districts O
where O
there O
was O
a O
high O
incidence O
of O
CMD B-DISEASE
in O
1990–92 B-DATE
. O

A O
- O
B O
- O
C O
manufacturing O
processes O
enabled O
75 O
% O
recovery O
of O
the O
starch O
present O
in O
fresh O
roots B-PLANT_PART
. O

In O
a O
shelf O
life O
study O
, O
banana B-CROP
jams O
stored O
at O
4 O
° O
C O
were O
found O
to O
have O
a O
longer O
shelf O
life O
compared O
to O
those O
stored O
at O
25 O
° O
C O
. O

Methods O
153:223 O
, O
2008 B-DATE
. O

Sucrose O
content O
increased O
by O
56 O
% O
for O
Heart O
- O
o O
- O
Gold O
over O
the B-DATE
12 I-DATE
weeks I-DATE
of O
assay O
, O
ranking O
first O
among O
the O
cultivars O
at O
17 O
and O
19 O
WAT O
and O
possessing O
27 O
% O
more O
sucrose O
than O
the O
next O
highest O
ranking O
cultivar O
, O
Jewel O
, O
at O
19 O
WAT O
. O

L. O

Flower B-PLANT_PART
removal O
: O
the O
flower B-PLANT_PART
structure O
of O
the O
plants O
was O
removed O
every O
15 B-DATE
d I-DATE
after O
emergence O
of O
the O
flower B-PLANT_PART
. O

Nematology O
6:303 O
, O
2004 B-DATE
. O

Finally O
, O
the O
entire O
plant O
collapses O
and O
dies O
. O

Out O
of O
the O
169 O
symptomatic O
samples O
collected O
from O
Benin B-GPE
, O
nine O
fungal O
genera O
were O
isolated O
: O
Aspergillus B-PATHOGEN
spp I-PATHOGEN
. O

DNA O
extracted O
from O
the O
resulting O
pure O
Rhizoctonia B-PATHOGEN
cultures I-PATHOGEN
was O
screened O
using O
a O
real O
- O
time O
PCR O
assay O
for O
AG3 B-PATHOGEN
- I-PATHOGEN
PT I-PATHOGEN
( O
3 O
) O
. O

Loebenstein O
et O
al O
. O

In O
2010 B-DATE
, O
more O
than O
60,000 O
ha O
were O
affected O
in O
Vietnam B-GPE
with O
crop O
losses O
as O
high O
as O
80 O
% O
, O
and O
reductions O
in O
yield O
and O
starch O
content O
reached O
30 O
% O
. O

The O
fruit B-PLANT_PART
was O
counted O
, O
weighed O
and O
stored O
in O
screen O
- O
covered O
plastic O
trays O
containing O
vermiculite O
and O
kept O
at O
room O
temperature O
. O

with O
typical O
bunchy O
top O
symptoms O
. O

Moisture O
loss O
from O
banana B-CROP
fritters O
with O
batter O
formulation O
of O
2 O
% O
PCN O
and O
10 O
% O
SPI O
was O
the O
lowest O
while O
the O
reduction O
in O
oil O
content O
( O
55 O
% O
) O
was O
the O
highest O
. O

They O
shed O
new O
light O
on O
the O
value O
of O
past O
breeding O
efforts O
to O
recreate O
the O
European B-LOC
potato B-CROP
from O
Andean B-GPE
forms O
and O
highlight O
the O
value O
of O
herbarium O
specimens O
in O
investigating O
origins O
of O
crop O
plants O
. O

BLAST O
analysis O
showed O
100 O
% O
identity O
to O
Ca B-PATHOGEN
. I-PATHOGEN
Phytoplasma I-PATHOGEN
australiense I-PATHOGEN
( O
16SrXII B-PATHOGEN
, O
Stolbur O
group O
) O
. O

1991 B-DATE
) O
and O
sequenced O
. O

( O
E. B-PATHOGEN
chrysanthemi I-PATHOGEN
) O
causing O
bacterial O
stem B-DISEASE
and I-DISEASE
root I-DISEASE
rot I-DISEASE
of O
sweetpotato B-CROP
in O
China B-GPE
. O

A O
representative O
sample O
from O
each O
location O
was O
selected O
and O
tested O
for O
the O
presence O
of O
Cucumber B-PATHOGEN
mosaic I-PATHOGEN
virus I-PATHOGEN
( O
CMV B-PATHOGEN
, O
genus O
Cucumovirus O
) O
, O
Banana B-PATHOGEN
streak I-PATHOGEN
virus I-PATHOGEN
( O
BSV B-PATHOGEN
, O
genus O
Badnavirus O
) O
, O
Banana B-PATHOGEN
mild I-PATHOGEN
mosaic I-PATHOGEN
virus I-PATHOGEN
( O
BanMMV B-PATHOGEN
, O
family O
Flexiviridae O
) O
, O
and O
Banana B-PATHOGEN
bract I-PATHOGEN
mosaic I-PATHOGEN
virus I-PATHOGEN
( O
BBrMV B-PATHOGEN
, O
genus O
Potyvirus O
) O
. O

ORCID O
: O
Arias O
, O
J.S. O

Chlorotic O
and O
necrotic O
local O
lesions O
developed O
on O
Chenopodium B-CROP
amaranticolor I-CROP
and O
Vigna B-CROP
unguiculata I-CROP
( O
cv O
. O

Flowers B-PLANT_PART
showed O
significant O
cupping O
and O
browning O
and O
growers O
report O
a O
reduction O
in O
size O
and O
shelf O
life O
. O

There O
was O
significantly O
higher O
unusable O
root B-PLANT_PART
incidence O
in O
recycled O
materials O
( O
3.7 O
% O
) O
than O
in O
new O
materials O
( O
1.4 O
% O
) O
in O
Masika O
but O
not O
in O
Vuli O
. O

Allergy O
to O
potato B-CROP
is O
uncommon O
, O
and O
allergic O
reactions O
to O
cooked O
potato B-CROP
have O
been O
reported O
only O
in O
children O
. O

The O
inoculating O
of O
the O
isolate O
in O
35 O
micropropagated O
seedlings O
of O
banana B-CROP
was O
based O
on O
Koch O
's O
postulates O
. O

Seedlings O
( O
20 O
to O
30 O
cm O
) O
were O
planted O
in O
10 O
- O
cm O
- O
diameter O
plastic O
pots O
containing O
sterilized O
field O
soil O
at O
room O
temperature O
. O

No O
hay O
diferencias O
estadísticas O
en O
la O
producción O
por O
planta O
, O
la O
producción O
con O
paclobutrazol O
fue O
de O
14 O
kg O
/ O
planta O
, O
el O
cloruro O
mepiquat O
15 O
kg O
/ O
planta O
y O
el O
control O
con O
14,5 O
kg O
/ O
planta O
. O

We O
found O
three O
B. O

Oil O
re O
- O
use O
is O
a O
common O
practice O
in O
households O
. O

M. O

Guangfen O
) O
in O
Guigang B-GPE
city O
( O
N22 B-LOC
° I-LOC
50'29″ I-LOC
, I-LOC
E109 I-LOC
° I-LOC
43'34″ I-LOC
) O
, O
Guangxi B-GPE
province O
, O
China B-GPE
. O

Los O
dos O
reguladores O
del O
crecimiento O
muestran O
una O
reducción O
de O
la O
altura O
de O
la O
planta O
antes O
de O
la O
emergencia O
de O
la O
flor O
, O
el O
paclobutrazol O
reduce O
la O
altura O
hasta O
un O
40 O
% O
, O
mientras O
que O
el O
cloruro O
de O
mepiquat O
reduce O
la O
altura O
hasta O
un O
6,7 O
% O
. O

Stevenson O
, O
R. O

Gevens O
. O

Mycol O
. O

To O
our O
knowledge O
, O
this O
is O
the O
first O
report O
of O
occurrence O
of O
a O
16SrXII B-PATHOGEN
group I-PATHOGEN
phytoplasma I-PATHOGEN
causing O
potato B-DISEASE
stolbur I-DISEASE
diseases I-DISEASE
caused O
in O
the O
Eastern B-LOC
and I-LOC
Southern I-LOC
Anatolia I-LOC
regions O
of O
Turkey B-GPE
. O

Dale O
. O

( O
4 O
) O
A. O

References O
: O
( O
1 O
) O
L. O

Res O
. O

This O
study O
reports O
an O
artificial O
diet O
- O
based O
multi O
- O
well O
plate O
method O
and O
the O
first O
findings O
on O
the O
potential O
application O
of O
biotechnology O
in O
the O
control O
of O
the O
banana O
weevil O
using O
dietary O
RNAi O
, O
which O
would O
arguably O
provide O
the O
most O
sustainable O
and O
practical O
method O
for O
dsRNA O
delivery O
. O

Arzanlou O
et O
al O
. O

Banana B-DISEASE
bunchy I-DISEASE
top I-DISEASE
disease I-DISEASE
is O
one O
of O
the O
most O
serious O
diseases O
of O
bananas B-CROP
( O
Musa B-CROP
spp I-CROP
. O

PCR O
primers O
, O
PSY680F O
5'-GTTCGGAATAACTGGGCGTA-3 O
and O
PSY1R O
5'-CCCATAAGGGCCATGAGGACT-3 O
, O
were O
used O
to O
amplify O
a O
680 O
- O
bp O
fragment O
of O
the O
16S O
rDNA O
for O
the O
recently O
described O
"""""""""" O
Candidatus B-PATHOGEN
Liberibacter I-PATHOGEN
physallaurous I-PATHOGEN
"""""""""" I-PATHOGEN
( O
2 O
) O
and O
"""""""""" O
Ca B-PATHOGEN
. I-PATHOGEN
L. I-PATHOGEN
solanacearum I-PATHOGEN
"""""""""" O
( O
3 O
) O
. O

Hence O
, O
prior O
knowledge O
of O
soil O
chemistry O
is O
crucial O
to O
determining O
suitable O
concrete O
grade O
and O
nominal O
cover O
for O
durable O
substructural O
elements O
. O

Corynespora B-PATHOGEN
cassiicola I-PATHOGEN
. O

S. O

This O
is O
the O
first O
report O
of O
isolates O
of O
AG-4 O
and O
AG-5 O
causing O
disease O
in O
potato B-CROP
crops O
in O
South B-LOC
Australia I-LOC
. O

Landrace B-CROP
potato I-CROP
cultivars O
are O
native O
to O
two O
areas O
in O
South B-LOC
America I-LOC
: O
the O
high B-LOC
Andes I-LOC
from O
eastern B-LOC
Venezuela I-LOC
to O
northern B-LOC
Argentina I-LOC
and O
the O
lowlands B-LOC
of I-LOC
south I-LOC
- I-LOC
central I-LOC
Chile I-LOC
. O

( O
Abstr O
. O

Seriously O
infected O
roots B-PLANT_PART
were O
malformed O
and O
dehiscent O
, O
with O
the O
tissue O
discolored O
and O
rotting O
. O

Firmicutes O
dominated O
the O
bacterial O
community O
of O
abacha O
and O
fufu O
, O
whereas O
, O
Proteobacteria O
was O
the O
dominant O
phylum O
in O
garri O
. O

Commonwealth B-ORG
Mycological I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
, O
Kew B-GPE
, O
UK B-GPE
1971 B-DATE
. O

Three O
samples O
reacted O
strongly O
with O
MAbs O
that O
could O
detect O
both O
ACMV B-PATHOGEN
and O
EACMV B-PATHOGEN
. O

2010 B-DATE
) O
( O
GenBank B-ORG
accession O
numbers O
: O
Seq1 O
OL802918 O
and O
Seq2 O
OL802919 O
) O
. O

Globally O
, O
cassava B-CROP
is O
an O
important O
food O
crop O
that O
contributes O
significantly O
to O
food O
security O
. O

The O
P. B-PATHOGEN
infestans I-PATHOGEN
clonal O
lineage O
US-23 O
was O
present O
in O
epidemics O
in O
2009 B-DATE
and I-DATE
2010 I-DATE
in O
the B-GPE
United I-GPE
States I-GPE
. O

Recently O
, O
two O
major O
mutations O
, O
H227R O
in O
SdhB O
and O
H133R O
in O
SdhD O
, O
have O
been O
identified O
in O
highly O
resistant O
A. B-PATHOGEN
solani I-PATHOGEN
isolates O
in O
Idaho B-GPE
( O
2 O
) O
. O

) O
Appel O
& O
Wollenw O
. O

, O
2003 B-DATE
) O
, O
Iranian B-GPE
BBTV B-PATHOGEN
isolates O
were O
divided O
into O
two O
distinct O
strains O
. O

Commonw O
. O

The O
sequences O
were O
subjected O
to O
a O
database O
search O
using O
BLAST O
to O
verify O
the O
identity O
. O

This O
is O
the O
first O
report O
of O
the O
use O
of O
M. B-CROP
azedarach I-CROP
callus O
against O
B. O

It O
has O
been O
shown O
( O
Quintiliano O
et O
al O
. O

The O
disease O
epidemic O
might O
have O
been O
enhanced O
by O
frequent O
hands O
- O
on O
activities O
in O
greenhouse O
tomato B-CROP
production O
and O
the O
environmental O
conditions O
( O
high O
temperature O
and O
intense O
lighting O
) O
in O
the O
greenhouse O
that O
favor O
symptom O
expression O
. O

1994 B-DATE
. O

The O
inoculation O
of O
three O
isolates O
was O
carried O
out O
in O
three O
plants O
, O
three O
leaves B-PLANT_PART
for O
each O
plant O
, O
by O
spraying O
spore O
solution O
with O
a O
concentration O
of O
1×106 O
conidia O
/ O
ml O
, O
without O
wounding O
the O
leaves B-PLANT_PART
and O
placed O
in O
a O
humid O
chamber O
at O
25 O
° O
C O
for O
ten B-DATE
days I-DATE
. O

In O
summer B-DATE
2012 I-DATE
, O
plants O
in O
potato B-CROP
fields O
in O
Idaho B-GPE
were O
sampled O
for O
R. B-PATHOGEN
solani I-PATHOGEN
. O

Goodwin O
et O
al O
. O

The O
disease O
was O
found O
to O
occur O
in O
the O
majority O
of O
commercial O
cultivars O
grown O
in O
different O
banana B-CROP
- O
growing O
states O
of O
India B-GPE
. O

Bateson O
and O
J. O

The O
compressive O
strength O
of O
concrete O
specimens O
in O
the O
two O
soil O
environments O
increased O
, O
though O
the O
trend O
was O
lower O
in O
the O
polluted O
soil O
. O

22:107 O
, O
1992 B-DATE
. O

All O
isolates O
phenotypically O
resembledF. O

Data O
collected O
in O
Munyika B-GPE
show O
that O
when O
appropriate O
cultural O
practices O
are O
applied O
and O
adhered O
to O
, O
within O
a B-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
BBTD B-DISEASE
incidence O
can O
be O
reduced O
to O
economically O
acceptable O
levels O
in O
an O
existing O
plantation O
( O
26.2 O
% O
to O
8.2 O
% O
) O
and O
in O
new O
plantations O
( O
2 O
% O
, O
FHIA O
trial O
) O
. O

2:45 O
, O
2005 B-DATE
. O

Banana B-DISEASE
finger I-DISEASE
- I-DISEASE
tip I-DISEASE
rot I-DISEASE
is O
an O
endemic O
minor O
disease O
in O
Taiwan B-GPE
. O

 O
similaris O
and O
E. O

Grand O
Naine O
. O

PurposeDeep O
- O
fried O
banana B-CROP
( O
Musa B-CROP
spp I-CROP
. O

Groups O
V O
and O
VI O
were O
more O
effective O
at O
inactivating O
AHLs O
. O

Experiments O
with O
Beauregard O
and O
Evangeline O
sweetpotato B-CROP
cuttings O
revealed O
differential O
adventitious O
root B-PLANT_PART
( O
AR O
) O
emergence O
responses O
to O
1 O
- O
MCP O
application O
. O

KASP O
SNP O
genotyping O
of O
B. O

Five O
30 O
- O
cm O
- O
long O
stem B-PLANT_PART
portions O
per O
isolate O
were O
cut O
from O
healthy O
cassava B-CROP
, O
surface O
disinfested O
in O
hot O
water O
( O
52 O
° O
C O
, O
5 B-DATE
min I-DATE
) O
, O
and O
planted O
into O
1 O
- O
liter O
pots O
containing O
autoclaved O
, O
sterilized O
sand O
mixed O
with O
10 O
ml O
of O
air O
- O
dried O
inoculum O
. O

2 O
: O
V065:1 O
, O
2007 B-DATE
. O

In O
the O
present O
finding O
, O
Homalotylus O
turkmenicus O
Myartseva O
is O
reported O
to O
be O
gregariously O
parasitizing O
grubs O
of O
Hyperaspis O
maindroni O
Sicard O
( O
Coleoptera O
: O
Coccinellidae O
) O
in O
the O
colonies O
of O
P. O

The O
isolates O
may O
not O
have O
been O
exposed O
to O
fludioxonil O
because O
currently O
applications O
are O
restricted O
to O
seed B-PLANT_PART
not O
intended O
for O
seed B-PLANT_PART
production O
( O
3 O
) O
. O

PLALA O

Crops O
, O
Nelspruit B-GPE
, O
South B-GPE
Africa I-GPE
. O

MZ768922 O
and O
OK668082 O
) O
showed O
> O
99 O
% O
identities O
to O
several O
records O
of O
Dickeya B-PATHOGEN
fangzhongdai I-PATHOGEN
deposited O
in O
NCBI B-ORG
GenBank B-ORG
( O
1400/1404 O
bps O
for O
GZF2 O
- O
2 O
to O
KT992690 O
, O
1409/1417 B-DATE
bps I-DATE
for O
GZF1 O
- O
8 O
to O
MT613398 O
) O
based O
on O
BLAST O
analysis O
. O

causing O
potato B-DISEASE
seed I-DISEASE
- I-DISEASE
piece I-DISEASE
decay I-DISEASE
. O

HM753555 O
) O
. O

Munyaneza O
et O
al O
. O

) O
, O
or O
not O
immersed O
( O
nontreated O
control O
) O
. O

References O
: O
( O
1 O
) O
A. O

Durability O
is O
the O
measure O
of O
the O
robustness O
of O
constructed O
facilities O
against O
deterioration O
tendencies O
. O

Aerial O
hyphae O
produced O
long O
branches O
that O
bore O
lateral O
chains O
of O
1 O
to O
7 O
conidia O
. O

The O
isolate O
, O
designated O
INSV O
pot O
1 O
, O
was O
mechanically O
inoculated O
to O
one O
plant O
of O
potato B-CROP
cv O
. O

Received O
: O
31 O
- O
07 O
- O
2020 O
Accepted O
: O
22 O
- O
11 O
- O
2020 O
Published O
: O
18 O
- O
12 O
- O
2020 O
INTRODUCTION O
2 O
ARIAS O
- O
GARCIA O
/ O
ARISTIZABAL O
- O
LOAIZA O
Rev. O

, O
polysaccharides O
and O
other O
plant O
polymers O
) O
. O

Results O
of O
sequence O
analysis O
showed O
the O
sequence O
of O
isolated O
strain O
H12 O
was O
99 O
% O
identical O
to O
that O
of O
E. B-PATHOGEN
chrysanthemi I-PATHOGEN
, O
99 O
% O
identical O
to O
that O
of O
type O
strain O
CFBP O
1269 O
T O
of O
Dickeya B-PATHOGEN
dadantii I-PATHOGEN
( O
Accession O
No O
. O

, O
2014 B-DATE
) O
. O

Phytosanitary O
leaf B-PLANT_PART
removal O
: O
Four B-DATE
months I-DATE
after O
planting O
, O
leaves B-PLANT_PART
with O
more O
than O
50 O
% O
of O
leaf B-PLANT_PART
area O
with O
necrosis O
resulting O
from O
Sigatoka B-DISEASE
were O
removed O
weekly O
. O

Snyd O
. O

The O
citrus O
mealybug O
( O
Planococus O
citri O
) O
has O
been O
shown O
to O
transmit O
banana B-PATHOGEN
streak I-PATHOGEN
virus I-PATHOGEN
( O
BSV B-PATHOGEN
) O
but O
not O
banana B-PATHOGEN
bunchy I-PATHOGEN
top I-PATHOGEN
virus I-PATHOGEN
or O
cucumber B-PATHOGEN
mosaic I-PATHOGEN
virus I-PATHOGEN
( O
CMV B-PATHOGEN
) O
( O
2 O
) O
. O

Phytopathol O
. O

The O
disease O
incidence O
was O
about O
10 O
to O
20 O
% O
. O

Diseased O
plants O
were O
often O
elongated O
and O
frail O
with O
spindly O
shoots B-PLANT_PART
. O

Initially O
, O
the O
leaves B-PLANT_PART
turn O
yellow O
, O
and O
a O
black O
, O
water O
- O
soaked O
rot O
occurs O
on O
the O
bottom O
of O
the O
stems B-PLANT_PART
that O
gradually O
extends O
to O
the O
top O
of O
the O
stems B-PLANT_PART
. O

Agric O
. O

Cassava B-CROP
is O
well O
adapted O
to O
poor O
or O
degraded O
soils O
because O
of O
its O
tolerance O
to O
low O
pH O
, O
high O
levels O
of O
exchangeable O
aluminium O
( O
Al O
) O
and O
low O
concentrations O
of O
phosphorus O
( O
P O
) O
in O
the O
soil O
solution O
. O

The O
suspension O
was O
diluted O
1000 O
times O
with O
sterilized O
water，then O
plated O
on O
nutrient O
- O
agar O
medium O
and O
incubated O
at O
28 O
℃ O
in O
darkness O
for O
24 B-DATE
h. I-DATE
Among O
the O
32 O
isolates O
, O
23 O
pure O
bacterial O
cultures O
with O
similar O
morphology O
were O
predominantly O
obtained O
from O
the O
samples O
. O

Use O
of O
the O
riboprobe O
hybridization O
assay O
should O
facilitate O
a O
more O
rapid O
detection O
of O
SPVD B-PATHOGEN
- I-PATHOGEN
aC I-PATHOGEN
infected O
sweet B-CROP
potato I-CROP
and O
subsequent O
selection O
of O
virus O
- O
free O
germ O
plasm O
for O
international O
exchange O
. O

Plant O
Pathol O
. O

Furthermore O
, O
we O
have O
discovered O
that O
for O
CBSV B-PATHOGEN
, O
rates O
of O
nonsynonomous O
substitutions O
are O
more O
predominant O
than O
synonymous O
substitution O
and O
occur O
across O
the O
entire O
genome O
. O

Zhang O
. O

1 O
) O
. O

Boher O
et O
al O
. O

EU849020 O
and O
EU919514 O
) O
. O

However O
, O
low O
adherence O
to O
proposed O
management O
practices O
underlines O
that O
most O
farmers O
– O
despite O
awareness O
raising O
are O
reluctant O
to O
uproot O
the O
entire O
mat O
( O
100 O
% O
of O
farmers O
) O
or O
the O
diseased O
corm B-PLANT_PART
( O
78 O
% O
of O
farmers O
) O
when O
a O
single O
plant O
manifests O
visible O
symptoms O
. O

Morphological O
identification O
and O
sequence O
analysis O
of O
ITS O
rDNA O
showed O
that O
the O
pathogen O
was O
B. B-PATHOGEN
setariae I-PATHOGEN
. O

1993 B-DATE
; O
Vetten O
et O
al O
. O

, O
2007 B-DATE
) O
, O
and O
reducing O
shoot B-PLANT_PART
elongation O
( O
Rademacher O
, O
2015 B-DATE
) O
, O
among O
others O
. O

All O
isolates O
were O
gram O
negative O
, O
aerobic O
, O
and O
grew O
at O
42 O
° O
C O
, O
positive O
for O
oxidase O
, O
lysine O
decarboxylase O
, O
and O
ornithine O
decarboxylase O
, O
but O
negative O
for O
arginine O
dihydrolase O
and O
tryptophanase O
( O
indole O
production O
) O
. O

Glucose O
content O
profiles O
were O
similar O
to O
those O
for O
fructose O
changes O
during O
development O
. O

sordidus O
. O

1998 B-DATE
; O
Maryani O
et O
al O
. O

J. O

93:108 O
, O
2009 O
. O

KC782951 O
) O
shared O
99 O
% O
identity O
with O
other O
AG O
- O
A O
isolates O
( O
AY927358 O
and O
AY927356 O
) O
. O

Sigatoka B-DISEASE
leaf I-DISEASE
diseases I-DISEASE
are O
a O
major O
constraint O
to O
banana B-CROP
production O
. O

Xu O
et O
al O
. O

Previously O
, O
a O
detection O
survey O
for O
BBTV B-PATHOGEN
was O
done O
in O
South B-GPE
Africa I-GPE
in O
1996 B-DATE
and O
this O
study O
confirmed O
the O
absence O
of O
BBTV B-PATHOGEN
in O
the O
Kiepersol B-GPE
region O
of O
Mpumalanga B-GPE
Province I-GPE
( O
Pietersen O
et O
al O
. O

J. O

Compared O
with O
the O
end O
of O
treatment O
, O
the O
above O
- O
mentioned O
indexes O
recurred O
insignificantly O
in O
the O
combination O
group O
and O
acupuncture O
group O
after O
64 B-DATE
weeks I-DATE
of O
follow O
- O
up O
( O
P>0.05 O
) O
, O
but O
all O
recurred O
significantly O
in O
the O
Plantain B-CROP
and O
Senna O
Granule O
group O
( O
P>0.05 O
) O
. O

However O
, O
when O
leaves B-PLANT_PART
were O
removed O
, O
no O
such O
increase O
was O
observed O
. O

Geering O
et O
al O
. O

Previous O
studies O
have O
documented O
CBSV B-PATHOGEN
is O
more O
devastating O
than O
UCBSV B-PATHOGEN
. O

Dep O
. O

J. O

The O
purple O
anthocyanins O
in O
potato B-CROP
tuber B-PLANT_PART
skin O
and O
flesh O
are O
primarily O
derived O
from O
petunidin O
. O

This O
effect O
may O
contribute O
, O
in O
part O
, O
to O
the O
ability O
of O
flavonoid O
- O
rich O
food O
to O
regulate O
glucose O
homeostasis O
of O
meals O
rich O
in O
available O
carbohydrates O
. O

Potato B-CROP
( O
Solanum B-CROP
tuberosum I-CROP
) O
is O
the O
second O
most O
important O
food O
crop O
in O
Kenya B-GPE
after O
maize B-CROP
( O
MOA B-ORG
, O
2007 B-DATE
) O
. O

Symptoms O
consisted O
of O
1- O
to O
3 O
- O
mm O
diameter O
black O
circular O
necrotic O
spots O
and O
appeared O
on O
the O
leaves B-PLANT_PART
of O
2- B-DATE
to I-DATE
3 I-DATE
- I-DATE
week I-DATE
- I-DATE
old I-DATE
plants O
. O

A O
strong O
linear O
relation- O
ship O
exists O
between O
fructose O
, O
glucose O
, O
and O
sucrose O
content O
in O
raw O
and O
baked O
roots B-PLANT_PART
( O
Lewthwaite O
et O
al O
. O

Disease O
symptoms O
associated O
with O
US-23 O
were O
observed O
exclusively O
on O
potato B-CROP
in O
2009 B-DATE
and O
on O
tomato B-CROP
in O
2010 B-DATE
in O
Wisconsin B-GPE
. O

, O
2015 B-DATE
) O
. O

55:1415 O
, O
2005 B-DATE
. O

( O
2 O
) O
Q. O

J. O

Partial O
cloning O
and O
sequence O
analysis O
of O
the O
dsRNA O
revealed O
95 O
to O
98 O
% O
nucleotide O
identity O
to O
sequences O
of O
P1 O
, O
HC O
- O
Pro O
, O
C1 O
, O
6K2 O
, O
VpG O
, O
NIb O
, O
and O
CP O
genes O
and O
the O
3 O
untranslated O
region O
( O
total O
approximately O
6 O
kb O
) O
of O
Banana B-PATHOGEN
bract I-PATHOGEN
mosaic I-PATHOGEN
virus I-PATHOGEN
( O
BBrMV B-PATHOGEN
) O
. O

, O
Kew B-GPE
, O
Surrey B-GPE
, O
UK B-GPE
, O
1972 B-DATE
. O

Can O
. O

Simple O
Summary O
We O
report O
here O
the O
first O
detailed O
characterization O
of O
Bemisia O
whiteflies O
on O
cassava B-CROP
in O
eastern B-LOC
Democratic I-LOC
Republic I-LOC
of I-LOC
Congo I-LOC
( O
DRC B-GPE
) O
. O

In O
the B-DATE
spring I-DATE
of I-DATE
2007 I-DATE
, O
samples O
of O
cut O
seed B-PLANT_PART
tubers B-PLANT_PART
( O
cvs O
. O

A O
certification O
system O
for O
seed B-PLANT_PART
potatoes B-CROP
does O
not O
exist O
in O
the O
country O
. O

After O
3 B-DATE
to I-DATE
4 I-DATE
days I-DATE
of O
inoculation O
, O
brown O
to O
black O
spotted O
lesions O
were O
observed O
and O
coalesced O
to O
become O
black O
sunken O
lesions O
. O

Conclusions O
This O
study O
is O
expected O
to O
provide O
insights O
into O
the O
incorporation O
of O
green O
banana B-CROP
into O
the O
dietary O
management O
of O
PD O
. O

Conclusions O
: O
To O
our O
knowledge O
, O
this O
is O
the O
first O
report O
on O
the O
construction O
of O
a O
genetic O
linkage O
map O
for O
purple B-CROP
sweetpotato I-CROP
( O
Jizishu O
1 O
) O
and O
the O
identification O
of O
QTLs O
associated O
with O
resistance O
to O
root B-DISEASE
rot I-DISEASE
in O
sweetpotato B-CROP
using O
SSR O
markers O
. O

92:1444 O
, O
2008 B-DATE
. O

L. O

It O
can O
be O
used O
as O
a O
potential O
substrate O
for O
cellulase O
production O
by O
T. O

Spots O
were O
dark O
brown O
or O
had O
white O
papery O
centers O
delimited O
by O
dark O
brown O
rims O
and O
surrounded O
by O
a O
yellow O
halo O
. O

The O
method O
of O
Wu O
and O
Su O
( O
1 O
) O
was O
used O
to O
purify O
the O
virus O
, O
and O
electron O
microscopy O
detected O
virus O
particles O
20 O
- O
22 O
nm O
in O
diameter O
. O

Two O
pieces O
were O
used O
as O
rootstocks O
in O
graft O
- O
inoculation O
tests O
with O
Secundina O
scions B-PLANT_PART
for O
FSD B-DISEASE
detection O
, O
and O
two O
pieces O
were O
potted O
in O
sterilized O
soil O
to O
be O
used O
in O
other O
tests O
. O

K. O

E. O

( O
2 O
) O
N. O

) O
de O
Bary O
is O
an O
important O
disease O
of O
potato B-CROP
and O
tomato B-CROP
that O
occurs O
annually O
in O
the O
hills O
and O
occasionally O
in O
the O
terai O
( O
plain O
) O
of O
Nepal B-GPE
. O

On O
the O
basis O
of O
these O
results O
, O
the O
root O
- O
knot O
nematodes O
isolated O
from O
banana B-CROP
in O
Nanjing B-GPE
County I-GPE
were O
confirmed O
as O
M. O

harveyi O
carried O
VGs O
coding O
for O
haemolysin O
, O
toxR O
and O
flagella O
; O
formed O
biofilm O
; O
and O
adhered O
to O
both O
cell O
lines O
. O

MH243795 O
, O
MH243769 O
, O
MH243793 O
, O
MH243789 O
, O
and O
MH243794 O
) O
and O
additional O
reference O
sequences O
of O
species O
within O
the O
section O
Porri O
confirmed O
that O
the O
five O
isolates O
( O
DA01 O
, O
DA02 O
, O
and O
DA03 O
from O
the O
Tipaza B-GPE
province O
; O
and O
DA06 O
and O
DA07 O
from O
the O
Alger B-GPE
province O
) O
could O
be O
assigned O
to O
A. B-PATHOGEN
linariae I-PATHOGEN
with O
100 O
% O
sequence O
similarity O
to O
a O
reference O
strain O
( O
CBS O
109161 O
; O
GenBank B-ORG
accession O
no O
. O

Choi O
et O
al O
. O

AF097532 O
) O
. O

, O
a O
species O
that O
has O
also O
a O
much O
broader O
plant O
host O
range O
( O
mostly O
found O
on O
maize B-CROP
) O
, O
this O
was O
only O
recently O
reported O
for O
F. B-PATHOGEN
musae I-PATHOGEN
[ O
7 O
] O
. O

) O
Phytopathology O
93(suppl.):S75 O
, O
2003 B-DATE
. O

Isolations O
from O
leaf B-PLANT_PART
lesions O
were O
made O
on O
V8 O
juice O
agar O
under O
aseptic O
conditions O
. O

However O
, O
a O
new O
variant O
of O
Foc B-PATHOGEN
, O
tropical B-PATHOGEN
race I-PATHOGEN
4 I-PATHOGEN
( O
TR4 B-PATHOGEN
) O
, O
was O
identified O
in O
Southeast B-LOC
Asia I-LOC
in O
1992 B-DATE
and O
has O
spread O
throughout O
the O
region O
( O
3 O
) O
. O

Komatipoort B-GPE
is O
currently O
the O
largest O
banana B-CROP
production O
region O
in O
South B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
. O

The O
relationship O
between O
monosaccha- O
rides O
was O
fructose O
= O
0.7207 O
× O
glucose O
+ O
0.0241 O
. O

In O
Southern B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
, O
banana B-CROP
production O
is O
under O
threat O
from O
a O
number O
of O
viral O
diseases O
, O
including O
Banana B-PATHOGEN
bunchy I-PATHOGEN
top I-PATHOGEN
virus I-PATHOGEN
( O
BBTV B-PATHOGEN
) O
( O
family O
Nanoviridae O
, O
genus O
Babuvirus O
) O
. O

Natural O
resistance O
has O
so O
far O
only O
been O
reported O
for O
CMD B-DISEASE
in O
cassava B-CROP
. O

Primers O
used O
were O
AAF2 O
( O
5'-TGCAATCAGCGTCAGTAACAAAT-3 O
) O
and O
AAR3 O
( O
5'-ATGGATGCTAGACCTTTGCTGAT-3 O
) O
, O
specifically O
designed O
for O
identification O
of O
A. B-PATHOGEN
alternata I-PATHOGEN
( O
4 O
) O
. O

The O
separation O
was O
achieved O
with O
a O
reverse O
phase O
C18 O
GraceSmart O
column O
( O
150 O
mm O
· O
4.6 O
mm O
, O
3 O
- O
mm O
particle O
size O
) O
from O
Grace B-ORG
Davison I-ORG
Discovery I-ORG
Sciences I-ORG
Corp I-ORG
( O
Deerfield B-GPE
, O
IL B-GPE
) O
. O

Phytopathology O
97:1112 O
, O
2007 B-DATE
. O

Transcripts O
were O
analysed O
using O
Grounded O
Theory O
Methodology O
. O

None O
of O
these O
species O
are O
pathogenic O
on O
banana B-CROP
and O
hence O
, O
these O
findings O
give O
an O
insight O
into O
the O
endophytic O
existence O
of O
Fusarium B-PATHOGEN
spp I-PATHOGEN
. O

( O
12.5 O
% O
) O
. O

These O
QTLs O
will O
have O
practical O
significance O
for O
the O
fine O
mapping O
of O
root B-DISEASE
rot I-DISEASE
resistance O
genes O
and O
play O
an O
important O
role O
in O
sweetpotato B-CROP
marker O
- O
assisted O
breeding O
. O

Karyotype O
analysis O
has O
shown O
predominance O
of O
chromosomes O
with O
centromeres O
in O
median O
position O
with O
a O
few O
submedian O
centromeres O
. O

2019 B-DATE
) O
. O

The O
collected O
samples O
were O
tested O
for O
infection O
using O
Blotter O
method O
. O

110:823 O
, O
2004 B-DATE
. O

References O
: O
( O
1 O
) O
S. O

This O
analysis O
is O
one O
of O
the O
first O
reports O
to O
examine O
the O
distribution O
of O
common B-PATHOGEN
scab I-PATHOGEN
- I-PATHOGEN
causing I-PATHOGEN
species I-PATHOGEN
in O
Germany B-GPE
. O

Fusarium B-DISEASE
wilt I-DISEASE
of O
bananas B-CROP
, O
commonly O
called O
Panama B-DISEASE
disease I-DISEASE
, O
is O
caused O
by O
a O
suite O
of O
Fusarium B-PATHOGEN
species I-PATHOGEN
. O

This O
represents O
the O
first O
report O
of O
complete O
ACMV B-PATHOGEN
and O
EACMV B-PATHOGEN
DNA O
- O
A O
sequences O
from O
Angola B-GPE
. O

In O
young O
petioles B-PLANT_PART
, O
preferential O
expression O
was O
observed O
in O
the O
epidermis O
, O
in O
the O
two O
first O
cortex O
cell O
layers O
, O
and O
in O
the O
endodermis O
together O
with O
pericycle O
cells O
and O
specific O
parenchymatic O
cells O
around O
the O
laticifers O
. O

Virol O
. O

This O
insect O
feeds O
on O
the O
roots B-PLANT_PART
, O
reducing O
quality O
and O
yield O
, O
and O
is O
the O
most O
important O
production O
constraint O
of O
sweetpotato B-CROP
in O
Africa B-LOC
. O

Studies O
were O
then O
carried O
out O
on O
the O
etiology O
of O
this O
disease O
to O
acquire O
information O
about O
its O
management O
. O

In O
parallel O
, O
two O
contrasting O
control O
sites O
( O
no O
awareness O
raising O
and O
no O
cultural O
practices O
) O
within O
Cibitoke B-GPE
were O
identified O
( O
Mparambo B-GPE
II I-GPE
, O
‘ O
Yangambi O
Km O
5 O
’ O
monocrop O
and O
Muyange B-GPE
, O
‘ O
Igitsiri’/’Igisahira O
’ O
( O
AAA O
- O
EA O
) O
intercrop O
) O
. O

Concrete O
research O
is O
gradually O
shifting O
from O
the O
conventional O
strength O
- O
based O
approach O
to O
durability O
- O
centred O
in O
the B-DATE
past I-DATE
decade I-DATE
. O

Anthranose B-DISEASE
is O
a O
well O
- O
known O
postharvest O
disease O
of O
banana B-CROP
and O
with O
high O
potential O
for O
damaging O
market O
value O
, O
as O
infection O
commonly O
occurs O
during O
storage O
. O

J. O

74:5862 O
, O
2008 B-DATE
. O

Sampling O
method O
. O

Rep. O

( O
2 O
) O
. O

Palabras O
clave O
adicionales O
: O
fertilización O
; O
partición O
de O
nutrientes O
; O
nutrición O
mineral O
; O
Musaceae O
. O

To O
the O
best O
of O
our O
knowledge O
, O
this O
is O
the O
first O
report O
of O
occurrence O
of O
EACMV B-PATHOGEN
- I-PATHOGEN
UG I-PATHOGEN
in O
a O
species O
of O
the O
family O
Bignoniaceae O
. O

The O
reliability O
of O
DArTseq O
markers O
was O
demonstrated O
by O
their O
power O
to O
discriminate O
isolates O
below O
the O
Fusarium B-PATHOGEN
spp I-PATHOGEN
. O

However O
, O
farmer O
access O
to O
brewers O
’ O
grains O
is O
limited O
to O
the O
immediate O
area O
in O
which O
beer O
factories O
are O
found O
. O

2017 B-DATE
; O
Zakaria O
et O
al O
. O

50(1 O
) O
JANUARY B-DATE
2015 I-DATE
rural O
families O
of O
drought O
- O
affected O
environments O
( O
Bashaasha O
et O
al O
. O

( O
2 O
) O
S. O

The O
identity O
was O
confirmed O
by O
the O
Fusarium B-ORG
Research I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
at O
Pennsylvania B-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
. O

( O
2019 B-DATE
) O
and O
included O
water O
controls O
, O
a O
Race B-PATHOGEN
1 I-PATHOGEN
isolate O
, O
which O
is O
not O
pathogenic O
on O
Cavendish B-CROP
, O
the O
three O
Colombian B-GPE
isolates O
Col O
2 O
, O
Col O
4 O
, O
and O
Col O
17 O
, O
and O
the O
II5 O
TR4 O
reference O
strain O
. O

sinaloensis O
- O
like O
, O
V. O

Banana B-CROP
is O
the O
fourth O
ranked O
horticulture O
crop O
in O
the O
world O
and O
first O
among O
the O
fruits B-PLANT_PART
( O
Surya O
Prabha O
and O
Satheesh O
Kumar O
, O
2015 B-DATE
) O
. O

Although O
EMDV B-PATHOGEN
is O
widespread O
in O
the O
Mediterranean B-LOC
region I-LOC
and O
the O
Middle B-LOC
East I-LOC
( O
Brunt O
et O
al O
. O

2012 B-DATE
) O
. O

PCR O
and O
Southern O
blot O
analysis O
confirmed O
the O
independent O
, O
transgenic O
nature O
of O
transformants O
and O
indicated O
single O
and O
multiple O
locus O
integrations O
. O

( O
2009 B-DATE
) O
observed O
that O
farmers O
have O
the O
same O
selection O
ability O
as O
breeders O
. O

( O
3 O
) O
H. O

Th O
. O

O. O

Mosa O
et O
al O
. O

96:1323 O
, O
2012 B-DATE
. O

torus O
in O
other O
parts O
of O
South B-LOC
and I-LOC
South I-LOC
East I-LOC
Asia I-LOC
, O
except O
Acropimpla O
sp O
. O

, O
2011 B-DATE
) O
. O

Silk O
75 B-DATE
days I-DATE
old I-DATE
, O
grown O
in O
pots O
with O
5 O
kg O
of O
sterile O
formulation O
of O
sand O
and O
soil O
, O
in O
1:1 O
. O

For O
pathogenicity O
test O
, O
12 O
sweet B-CROP
potatoes I-CROP
were O
artificially O
inoculated O
with O
a O
representative O
fungus O
. O

SACMV B-PATHOGEN
is O
most O
closely O
related O
to O
East B-PATHOGEN
African I-PATHOGEN
cassava I-PATHOGEN
mosaic I-PATHOGEN
virus I-PATHOGEN
( O
EACMV B-PATHOGEN
) O
in O
both O
its O
DNA O
- O
A O
( O
85 O
% O
with O
EACMV B-PATHOGEN
- I-PATHOGEN
MH I-PATHOGEN
and I-PATHOGEN
-MK I-PATHOGEN
) O
and O
-B O
( O
90 O
% O
with O
EACMV B-PATHOGEN
- I-PATHOGEN
UG2 I-PATHOGEN
- I-PATHOGEN
Mld I-PATHOGEN
and O
EACMV B-PATHOGEN
- I-PATHOGEN
UG3 I-PATHOGEN
- I-PATHOGEN
Svr I-PATHOGEN
) O
components O
; O
however O
, O
percentage O
sequence O
similarities O
of O
less O
than O
90 O
% O
in O
the O
DNA O
- O
A O
component O
allowed O
SACMV B-PATHOGEN
to O
be O
considered O
a O
distinct O
virus O
. O

